<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
    <Entrys>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Philip Green named over harassment claims</Title>
            <Description>The retail billionaire is named in Parliament as the man facing newspaper allegations of sexual harassment.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45981436</URL>
            <Date>15:48 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Sir Philip Green named in Lords over harassment claims</Title>
            <Description>Speaking in the House of Lords, Lord Hain said it was in the public interest to reveal his name.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45983550</URL>
            <Date>14:57 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>SAS: Women allowed to join for first time</Title>
            <Description>Gavin Williamson says women will now be able apply for any military role, including the special forces.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45983882</URL>
            <Date>16:10 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Suspect package found at De Niro restaurant</Title>
            <Description>Police investigate a package at the New York restaurant owned by the actor, the FBI says.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45975447</URL>
            <Date>16:23 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Russian spy poisoning: Why was Sergei Skripal attacked?</Title>
            <Description>Evidence suggests the former spy was active across Europe, perhaps even investigating the Russian mafia.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45979830</URL>
            <Date>11:40 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>New York silicone death: Briton Donna Francis &apos;should be deported&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Kelly Mayhew died after having cosmetic surgery injections in New York in 2015.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-essex-45980070</URL>
            <Date>12:34 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Ed Farmer inquest: Student died from &apos;toxic effects&apos; of alcohol</Title>
            <Description>Ed Farmer died after suffering a cardiac arrest caused by excessive alcohol, an inquest hears.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-tyne-45979243</URL>
            <Date>16:01 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Home secretary apologises for immigrant DNA tests</Title>
            <Description>The home secretary says people were wrongly forced to take tests to prove their right to be in the UK.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45979359</URL>
            <Date>15:29 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Rise in women having induced labours, NHS figures show</Title>
            <Description>More older and overweight women giving birth is behind the trend, doctors say.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-45978623</URL>
            <Date>16:19 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;Spider-Man&apos; Alain Robert scales London&apos;s Heron Tower</Title>
            <Description>French urban climber Alain Robert climbs one of London&apos;s tallest buildings without safety gear.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-london-45980597</URL>
            <Date>15:21 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Man, 102, stuck on roof in Devon for three days</Title>
            <Description>He was rescued from the flat roof by firefighters after neighbours noticed he had not been seen.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-devon-45972639</URL>
            <Date>10:04 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>David Schwimmer: Blackpool Police identify Friends lookalike theft suspect</Title>
            <Description>Police say they are &quot;overwhelmed&quot; with the response to their social media appeal.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-lancashire-45982216</URL>
            <Date>15:28 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Sainsbury&apos;s to open Oasis clothes outlets in supermarkets</Title>
            <Description>The supermarket hopes the High Street chain will help make it a &quot;fashion destination&quot;.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45977660</URL>
            <Date>11:14 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>On America&apos;s trail of destruction</Title>
            <Description>Authorities have seized enough fentanyl to kill every American. It&apos;s a crisis that lines one major highway.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45968955</URL>
            <Date>21:14 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Gaza protest image likened to famous Delacroix painting</Title>
            <Description>A striking image of a Palestinian with a flag and sling is both admired and reviled on social media.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/blogs-trending-45975650</URL>
            <Date>12:54 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Labour&apos;s John McDonnell injures face in fall</Title>
            <Description>The Labour MP injured his face after tripping over some rubbish.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45981420</URL>
            <Date>12:43 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>White poppy: How is it different from the red remembrance symbol?</Title>
            <Description>Red, white or purple: does it matter what colour marks Remembrance Day?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45971456</URL>
            <Date>8:32 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The clocks go back and cold weather is on its way: Some tips to help you cope</Title>
            <Description>Winter is coming, as the clocks go back and temperatures are set to fall. So are you prepared?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45963190</URL>
            <Date>8:33 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Red Dead Redemption 2: A &apos;leap forward&apos; for Rockstar</Title>
            <Description>The makers of Grand Theft Auto talk to Newsbeat about their latest project, Red Dead Redemption 2.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45959083</URL>
            <Date>0:04 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Former Verve frontman Richard Ashcroft leaps over TV sofa</Title>
            <Description>Former Verve frontman surprises BBC presenters by exploring the set.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45979360</URL>
            <Date>10:58 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The disability vehicle so tiny it couldn&apos;t take passengers</Title>
            <Description>For decades, disabled people in the UK were given strange, three-wheeled cars that couldn&apos;t carry passengers and were later found to be so unsafe they were taken off the road.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45907925</URL>
            <Date>0:02 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Spectacular sunsets light up UK skies</Title>
            <Description>As spectacular sunsets light up the skies in the UK, we share the best snaps and explain the deep colours</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45973366</URL>
            <Date>21:51 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC News Channel</Title>
            <Description>BBC coverage of latest developments</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10318089</URL>
            <Date>20:19 10/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;The food supplement that ruined my liver&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Jim McCants took a food supplement to help him get healthy in middle age, but it left him in need of an urgent liver transplant.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45971416</URL>
            <Date>23:39 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Sexually transmitted infections: What to do if you get one</Title>
            <Description>Don&apos;t panic - these are the steps you need to take if you have an STI.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45975236</URL>
            <Date>14:14 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Reality Check: Which form of renewable energy is cheapest?</Title>
            <Description>Caroline Lucas MP says that onshore wind energy is the cheapest. What are the figures behind her claim?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45881551</URL>
            <Date>23:18 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Letter from Africa: I was tortured in The Gambia</Title>
            <Description>Lamin Cham explains why he wants to testify at The Gambia&apos;s new truth and reconciliation commission.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-africa-45917294</URL>
            <Date>23:46 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Migrant caravan: What is it and why does it matter?</Title>
            <Description>Thousands of migrants have been travelling by foot towards the US-Mexico border. Here&apos;s what we know.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-latin-america-45951782</URL>
            <Date>23:45 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Farrokh Bulsara: The Indian heritage of Freddie Mercury</Title>
            <Description>Nalini Sivathasan talks to some of London&apos;s Parsi community who can&apos;t wait to see him brought back to life on screen.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45973637</URL>
            <Date>23:18 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Fleabag star Maddie tackles a silent issue on stage</Title>
            <Description>Maddie Rice explains why her one-woman play is all about the importance of speaking out.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45966385</URL>
            <Date>23:05 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Ko Ko Korina: A bad cover version, the angry minister and Spiderman too</Title>
            <Description>Imagine if Ed Sheeran badly covered Bohemian Rhapsody - that&apos;s akin to what just happened in Pakistan.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-45961745</URL>
            <Date>23:01 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Deep division in Brazil&apos;s north-east, where &apos;life is real&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Brazil&apos;s poor Pernambuco state is deeply divided ahead of presidential elections on Sunday.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-latin-america-45965925</URL>
            <Date>23:41 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Jamal Khashoggi murder: What is Turkey&apos;s game with Saudi Arabia?</Title>
            <Description>Turkey&apos;s President Erdogan has been restrained in his criticism of Saudi Arabia. Mark Lowen asks why.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45963642</URL>
            <Date>11:38 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Pep Guardiola: The six songs that define my life, love, football and family</Title>
            <Description>Manchester City manager Pep Guardiola speaks exclusively &amp; in depth with BBC Radio 5 live about his life, career and favourite music.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45918581</URL>
            <Date>5:13 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Tour de France: Geraint Thomas eyes joint Team Sky lead after route unveiled</Title>
            <Description>Tour de France champion Geraint Thomas says he expects to be Team Sky&apos;s joint leader with Chris Froome next year following the route presentation.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/cycling/45975597</URL>
            <Date>15:21 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kyle Edmund out of Vienna Open after losing to Fernando Verdasco in second round</Title>
            <Description>British number one Kyle Edmund is out of the Vienna Open after losing in the second round to Spain&apos;s Fernando Verdasco.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/tennis/45983742</URL>
            <Date>15:25 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Marcelo Brozovic: Inter Milan midfielder hides behind wall to stop Luis Suarez free-kick</Title>
            <Description>Inter Milan midfielder Marcelo Brozovic has an ingenious idea to stop a Luis Suarez free-kick, by lying down behind the wall... and it worked.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45973546</URL>
            <Date>22:09 24/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>England v New Zealand: Kallum Watkins on why you need to watch the Test series</Title>
            <Description>Leeds Rhinos captain Kallum Watkins gives us his reasons why the three-Test series between England and New Zealand is a must-watch.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/av/rugby-league/45981327</URL>
            <Date>14:59 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Saudi Arabia&apos;s missing princes</Title>
            <Description>In the last two years, three Saudi princes living in Europe have disappeared. All were critical of the Saudi government.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-40926963</URL>
            <Date>23:57 14/8/2017</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The tip-off from a Nazi that saved my grandparents</Title>
            <Description>A Jewish tailor was advised to flee Denmark in 1943 by a German client. But why would this leading Nazi defy Hitler?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45919900</URL>
            <Date>23:47 20/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>My cheating boyfriend gave me HIV - here&apos;s how I got justice</Title>
            <Description>When Diane Reeve discovered that her partner was sleeping around she ended their relationship, but then she found out that he had given her HIV.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45626460</URL>
            <Date>23:58 17/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Philip Green named over harassment claims</Title>
            <Description>The retail billionaire is named in Parliament as the man facing newspaper allegations of sexual harassment.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45981436</URL>
            <Date>15:48 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Philip Green named over harassment claims</Title>
            <Description>The retail billionaire is named in Parliament as the man facing newspaper allegations of sexual harassment.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45981436</URL>
            <Date>15:48 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Philip Green named over harassment claims</Title>
            <Description>The retail billionaire is named in Parliament as the man facing newspaper allegations of sexual harassment.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45981436</URL>
            <Date>15:48 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Philip Green named over harassment claims</Title>
            <Description>The retail billionaire is named in Parliament as the man facing newspaper allegations of sexual harassment.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45981436</URL>
            <Date>15:48 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Philip Green named over harassment claims </Title>
            <Description>The retail billionaire is named in Parliament as the man facing newspaper allegations of sexual harassment.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45981436</URL>
            <Date>15:48 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
    </Entrys>
</root>
