<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
    <Entrys>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hurricane Florence: Life-threatening storm to soon hit North Carolina</Title>
            <Description>Officials warn Hurricane Florence could kill &quot;a lot of people&quot; as it nears the US East Coast.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45517260</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:27:03 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Prison staff protesting over inmate violence - POA union</Title>
            <Description>Protests are being held at &quot;the majority&quot; of prisons, but the government says the action is illegal.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45518744</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:34:58 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lehman anniversary: The five most surprising consequences</Title>
            <Description>A decade on, some of the big consequences of the financial crisis are also the most surprising.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45478670</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 21:53:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Westminster inquest: Court shown moment PC Keith Palmer stabbed</Title>
            <Description>&quot;Distressing&quot; footage is shown in court of the moment he was stabbed during the 2017 Westminster attack.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45522294</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:45:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Skripal Novichok poising: RT editor hangs up on Newsnight</Title>
            <Description>The journalist who interviewed the suspects in the Novichok attack took offence at Kirsty Wark&apos;s question.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45517388</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 02:11:33 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Ex-JLS member Oritse Williams charged with Wolverhampton rape</Title>
            <Description>Oritse Williams, 31, allegedly raped a fan in a hotel room after a concert in 2016.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-birmingham-45518544</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 08:10:08 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kimora Zondo, 7, died after hood caught on door</Title>
            <Description>There is &quot;no evidence&quot; of how Kimora Zondo became caught after reconstructions ruled out possibilities.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45519785</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:40:18 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lee Rigby: Fundraiser Gary Gardner jailed for fraud</Title>
            <Description>Lee Rigby&apos;s family said they &quot;never received a penny from&quot; Gary Gardner.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-leicestershire-45522484</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:52:35 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Wetherspoons warns of pricier pints</Title>
            <Description>Pub chain reports record sales and profits but says its rock-bottom prices are likely to rise.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45518774</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 07:26:00 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Brexit: Bank chief makes property crash warning</Title>
            <Description>Bank of England governor Mark Carney tells the cabinet a no-deal Brexit could see home prices plunge.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45516678</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:06:51 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hundreds stranded on new high-speed train in Devon</Title>
            <Description>Passengers had to be evacuated from the Hitachi 800 after it broke down in Devon.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-cornwall-45519014</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:01:39 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Super Typhoon Mangkhut: &apos;People tying down roofs&apos;</Title>
            <Description>People in the Philippines are preparing for the worst as Typhoon Mangkhut powers towards them.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-45518464</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 06:34:36 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Big Brother and Celebrity Big Brother are officially ending</Title>
            <Description>Show makers announced on Friday that the 19th series of the Channel 5 show would be its last.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45519752</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:56:15 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The Papers: Russia&apos;s &apos;insult&apos; and Carney&apos;s warning</Title>
            <Description>An &quot;extraordinary&quot; interview on Russian TV and a Bank of England Brexit briefing make the front pages.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/blogs-the-papers-45517066</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 05:04:42 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Uranus Examiner: Local newspaper stirs controversy</Title>
            <Description>An unusually named town in Missouri is stirring controversy with the title of its new newspaper.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45519884</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:46:50 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Quiz of the Week: Who sang Naomi to victory?</Title>
            <Description>It&apos;s the weekly news quiz - have you been paying attention to what&apos;s been going on in the world over the past seven days?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45511452</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:40:24 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nottingham make-up artist&apos;s surreal work is Instagram hit</Title>
            <Description>Romanie Jade-Tulloch&apos;s mind-bending artworks can take five hours to create.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-nottinghamshire-45514535</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:23:48 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The Skripal suspects&apos; walk through Salisbury</Title>
            <Description>Two suspects in the poisoning of a Russian ex-spy in the UK have said they were merely tourists.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45515013</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:03:15 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nintendo announces raft of new games for Switch console</Title>
            <Description>The Japanese firm announces a range of new games for its console - as well as a new retro controller.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-45520504</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:28:09 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Reviving Italy&apos;s ghost towns with an unusual hotel</Title>
            <Description>An unusual hotel, scattered throughout the community, is breathing life back into deserted villages.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45437803</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:41:13 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Being 18 on UK&apos;s Rathlin Island</Title>
            <Description>Benedict Anslow talks about what life is like as one of the few young people on Rathlin Island.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-northern-ireland-45500374</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:50:50 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Schoolboy crush pair wed in Leicestershire 60 years later</Title>
            <Description>Eric and Elaine Bogliani marry in the classroom where they met aged seven and nine.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-leicestershire-45514533</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:58:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC News Channel</Title>
            <Description>BBC coverage of latest developments</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10318089</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:55:21 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Why Afghanistan is more dangerous than ever</Title>
            <Description>The Taliban are mounting deadly attacks across Afghanistan, and the 17-year war has no clear end in sight.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-45507560</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:21:56 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The first lady of Jacobean Sex Comedy</Title>
            <Description>Funny and Forgotten: How history ignored the first lady of rom-com.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45433726</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:12:41 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Facebook UK boss: We want to give users more control</Title>
            <Description>Steve Hatch says Facebook could do a &quot;much better job&quot; of helping users control their experience.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45516746</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 20:14:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>From Mars Bars to Thunderbirds: Eight things Slough gave the world</Title>
            <Description>Slough received its Royal Charter 80 years ago - but what has the Berkshire town given to the world?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-berkshire-45420755</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:25:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Crowdfunded cancer treatments - do they work?</Title>
            <Description>Experts are concerned vulnerable patients are being exploited.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-45509942</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 07:50:50 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hurricane Florence: Four reasons to fear this storm</Title>
            <Description>Why it couldn&apos;t hit a worse area in the US</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45504866</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 22:42:00 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Crazy Rich Asians: Henry Golding on becoming a leading man in his first film</Title>
            <Description>Henry Golding on how it feels to swap being a journalist for a film star.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45498674</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 01:38:27 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>‘Why I filmed a man take his final breath&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Documentary maker Steven Eastwood says he filmed four terminally ill people to explore the reality of death.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45483616</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:45:53 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Can the city of pizza reinvent itself as a tech capital?</Title>
            <Description>How a city best known for pizza, football and crime is embracing tech to revive its fortunes.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45486674</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:16:40 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>French heritage lottery aims to save national treasures</Title>
            <Description>France&apos;s new lottery is raising money for hundreds of historic buildings - borrowing a British idea.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45509572</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:16:00 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Singapore GP: Daniel Ricciardo fastest as Charles Leclerc hits wall</Title>
            <Description>Daniel Ricciardo is fastest in Singapore GP first practice as Kimi Raikkonen&apos;s Ferrari replacement Charles Leclerc crashes into a wall.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/formula1/45519704</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:40:14 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Romelu Lukaku: Man Utd boss Jose Mourinho &apos;does not fake emotions&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Manchester United striker Romelu Lukaku tells BBC Sport about &quot;real&quot; manager Jose Mourinho and being schooled by Didier Drogba and Thierry Henry.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45516847</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:06:20 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Serena Williams: Jamie Murray says men do not get preferential treatment</Title>
            <Description>Jamie Murray says claims men are treated more leniently than women by tennis umpires is &quot;a bit far-fetched&quot;.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/tennis/45513038</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 18:58:36 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Dawid Godziek land&apos;s first quadruple tail whip on a mountain bike</Title>
            <Description>Watch Polish rider Dawid Godziek land the world&apos;s first quadruple tail whip on a mountain bike.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/cycling/45514844</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:08:02 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Premier League predictions: Lawro v actor Mark Wahlberg</Title>
            <Description>BBC Sport football pundit Mark Lawrenson takes on actor Mark Wahlberg to predict this weekend&apos;s Premier League results.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45435523</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 19:25:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Recovery and clouds on the Spanish horizon</Title>
            <Description>Ten years on from Spain&apos;s financial crisis, it&apos;s possible to see recovery and clouds on the horizon.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45485657</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:09:33 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;I lost my dream job at Lehman and now make pasta&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Natalia Rogoff lost her &quot;dream job&quot; when Lehman Brothers went bust, she then set up a pasta business.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45501476</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:10:33 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>How the financial crash provided some a new life and new hope</Title>
            <Description>Two women tell the BBC how the financial crash had a devastating but also positive impact on their lives.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45334996</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:11:28 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>How did the financial crisis affect your finances?</Title>
            <Description>A decade on, the way we deal with our personal finances has changed - but not always for good.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45483636</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 23:04:32 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Who was to blame for the financial crisis?</Title>
            <Description>BBC Business editor Simon Jack explores who could have been to blame for the global financial crisis.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45489064</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 23:19:42 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Paul McCartney on handling crowds, and why he calls Donald Trump &quot;the mad captain&quot;</Title>
            <Description>The star also says he can take the train to London without being spotted. But how?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45482360</URL>
            <Date>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 23:58:02 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kristina Vogel on crash that left her paralysed: &apos;I&apos;ve learned it is OK to cry at how bad it is&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Double Olympic cycling champion Kristina Vogel on coming to terms with the crash that has left her paralysed.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/cycling/45503798</URL>
            <Date>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 20:47:51 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Fenella Fielding, Sixties femme fatale</Title>
            <Description>Carry On Screaming actress and &quot;England&apos;s First Lady of the double entendre&quot; dies at 90.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/45409341</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:18:48 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Skripal Novichok poisoning: RT editor hangs up on Newsnight</Title>
            <Description>The journalist who interviewed the suspects in the Novichok attack took offence at Kirsty Wark&apos;s question.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45517388</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 02:11:33 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Electoral Commission got Brexit law wrong over Vote Leave, court rules</Title>
            <Description>The Electoral Commission loses a High Court case over its policing of Vote Leave&apos;s referendum spending.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45519676</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:09:13 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC Politics Live</Title>
            <Description>Live coverage of the day&apos;s politics from Westminster.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-24618323</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 11:26:10 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Super League: Clubs vote to scrap Super 8s in favour of &apos;one up, one down&apos; system</Title>
            <Description>Rugby league clubs vote to scrap the Super 8s format and return to a conventional promotion and relegation system from 2019.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/rugby-league/45520586</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:39:04 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hurricane Florence: Life-threatening storm lands in North Carolina</Title>
            <Description>Officials warn Hurricane Florence could kill &quot;a lot of people&quot; as it hits the US East Coast.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45517260</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:58:35 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Fiona Scourfield death: Boy killed stepmum with samurai sword</Title>
            <Description>Rueben Brathwaite will serve 15 years for killing Fiona Scourfield with an axe and samurai sword.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45522338</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:02:24 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC News at One</Title>
            <Description>BBC coverage of latest developments</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10318089</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:55:21 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Fraud ringleader jailed over &apos;boiler room&apos; scam</Title>
            <Description>The ringleader of a scam designed to con 170 investors out of £2.8m has been sent to prison.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45521235</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:10:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Skripal case: Russian &apos;spies&apos; targeted Swiss lab</Title>
            <Description>Russians were reportedly caught spying on a Swiss lab involved in the Salisbury poisoning inquiry.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45522614</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:15:27 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Prison staff protest over &apos;unprecedented&apos; inmate violence</Title>
            <Description>Officers say they face attacks by groups of prisoners, being spat at and having urine thrown at them.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45518744</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:38:11 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Boy murdered stepmum Fiona Scourfield with samurai sword</Title>
            <Description>A teenager &quot;obsessed&quot; with extreme violence tried to upload pictures of her body to the internet.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45522338</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:51:39 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>World Afro Day: ‘Why I love my natural hair’</Title>
            <Description>Women talk about why they love their natural hair.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45524065</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:44:44 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Electoral Commission &apos;misinterpreted&apos; Vote Leave expenses, court rules</Title>
            <Description>The Electoral Commission loses a High Court case over its policing of Vote Leave&apos;s referendum spending.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45519676</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:15:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Trump ex-campaign chief Manafort to help Mueller inquiry in plea deal</Title>
            <Description>In a plea deal, the former Trump campaign chairman also pleads guilty to two criminal charges.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45525325</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:35:25 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>House of Fraser online customers refused refunds</Title>
            <Description>Sports Direct, the chain&apos;s new owner, says it won&apos;t give refunds for goods ordered before the takeover.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45520194</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:49:37 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Salford fatal fire: Arson death children &apos;angels in the sky&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Mourners at the funeral of the four children hear a tribute from their mother, who could not attend.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-manchester-45519364</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:35:41 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kate Moss regrets &apos;nothing tastes as good as skinny feels&apos; comment</Title>
            <Description>Almost ten years on from the model&apos;s controversial mantra, she explains why she got it wrong.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45522714</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:27:07 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Backlash over Arriva Trains Wales lost wallet return charge</Title>
            <Description>Adam Howells had to pay more than £10 to Arriva Trains Wales to have his wallet returned.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45519994</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:55:38 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Maps: Where has Hurricane Florence hit?</Title>
            <Description>Satellite images, maps and graphics showing where the category one storm will hit and the impact it is expected to have.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45511312</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:31:19 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;My girl&apos;s meningitis was diagnosed as ear infection&apos;</Title>
            <Description>A charity warns the NHS must be more vigilant over deadly meningitis and sepsis cases.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-45501854</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:37:53 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>YouTube nursery-rhyme channel with billions of views sold</Title>
            <Description>The Little Baby Bum channel has racked up more than 17.5 billion views.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-45523304</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:13:36 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Maniac: Mixed reviews for Emma Stone&apos;s Netflix show</Title>
            <Description>The psychological dark comedy series stars Hollywood royalty Emma Stone and Jonah Hill.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45519744</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:00:11 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Shoplifters and a law that doesn&apos;t deter them</Title>
            <Description>A shopkeeper says he is losing thousands of pounds of stock each month, as figures show arrests are falling.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45512468</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:08:23 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Jose Mourinho: Man Utd boss defends Marcus Rashford playing time</Title>
            <Description>Manchester United boss Jose Mourinho defends his use of Marcus Rashford following claims the striker is not getting enough game time.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45519863</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:52:01 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Singapore GP: Kimi Raikkonen top as Sebastian Vettel hits wall</Title>
            <Description>Ferrari&apos;s Kimi Raikkonen leads Lewis Hamilton&apos;s Mercedes by just 0.011 seconds in second practice at the Singapore Grand Prix.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/formula1/45522627</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:20:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Davis Cup 2018: Great Britain lead Uzbekistan after Dan Evans beats Denis Istomin</Title>
            <Description>Dan Evans puts Great Britain ahead in their Davis Cup tie against Uzbekistan with victory over Denis Istomin in a gripping opening singles rubber.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/tennis/45524155</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:26:58 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Typhoon Mangkhut: Philippines braces for &apos;strongest&apos; storm</Title>
            <Description>The storm, described by forecasters as the strongest this year, is set to make landfall soon.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-45517803</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:53:19 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC News at Six</Title>
            <Description>BBC coverage of latest developments</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10318089</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:55:21 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Vuelta a Espana 2018: Simon Yates increases lead to over a minute after stage 19</Title>
            <Description>Simon Yates extends his lead at the Vuelta a Espana to one minute 38 seconds after finishing second in stage 19.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/cycling/45526525</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:30:27 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Manafort plea deal: Trump ex-campaign chief to help Mueller inquiry</Title>
            <Description>In a plea deal, the ex-Trump campaign chief admits two charges and will aid the Russia probe.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45525325</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 17:07:12 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hurricanes and typhoons: How to survive a major storm</Title>
            <Description>Two huge storms are threatening people on opposite sides of the world. Here&apos;s how to cope.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-45521927</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:56:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>UK &apos;should not favour&apos; EU workers post Brexit</Title>
            <Description>The Migration Advisory Committee also calls for an end to the limit of skilled workers coming to the UK.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45556246</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:49:16 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Russia blames Israel after military plane shot down off Syria</Title>
            <Description>The aircraft vanished after Israeli jets put it into the path of Syrian air defence, Moscow says.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45556290</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:35:03 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Men acquitted over fatal SAS march</Title>
            <Description>Three reservists died after a selection exercise in the Brecon Beacons on one of the hottest days of 2013.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45557588</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:38:40 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Celia Barquín: European golf champion murdered in Iowa</Title>
            <Description>A man is charged with murder after Spanish golfer Celia Barquín is found dead on an Iowa golf course.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45558504</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:58:01 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Emmy Awards 2018: Thandie Newton and Claire Foy among British winners</Title>
            <Description>Thandie Newton, Charlie Brooker and Claire Foy are among the winners at the 70th annual Primetime Emmys.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45495225</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 05:34:23 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>PM&apos;s wedding crasher photo surprise for Cowes couple</Title>
            <Description>A photographer captures the &quot;surreal&quot; moment the Prime Minister joins a newlywed couple for a photo.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-hampshire-45558945</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:27:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Footballer, 29, retires after MND diagnosis</Title>
            <Description>Bolton defender Stephen Darby retires from football, aged 29, after being diagnosed with motor neurone disease.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45561264</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:55:30 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Man who shot council officer on TV dies</Title>
            <Description>Albert Dryden, who shot a council officer in front of TV cameras, was freed in 2017 after a stroke.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-tyne-45557805</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:14:26 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Educating Greater Manchester head Drew Povey resigns</Title>
            <Description>Drew Povey, of Harrop Fold School, starred in Channel 4&apos;s Educating Greater Manchester.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-manchester-45558565</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:13:49 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Burns survivor in London Fashion Week show</Title>
            <Description>Catrin Pugh had to undergo 200 operations after a bus crash in the French Alps in 2013.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45557486</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:20:42 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>US imposes new tariffs on $200bn of Chinese goods</Title>
            <Description>The new taxes target $200bn worth of Chinese goods, marking the largest round of US tariffs so far.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45555749</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 07:37:48 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Storm Ali approach brings amber weather warning</Title>
            <Description>The Met Office warns of winds of up to 80 mph, which could endanger life.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45561524</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:33:30 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Billy Joe Saunders sorry after offering woman drugs</Title>
            <Description>Police are investigating a video of world boxing champion Billy Joe Saunders offering a woman drugs.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45559904</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:41:43 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Marriage proposal wins best Emmy moment</Title>
            <Description>The director gave an acceptance speech with a difference at the awards ceremony in LA.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45558324</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 06:49:34 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Emmy Awards 2018 red carpet fashion - in pictures</Title>
            <Description>Take a look at the stars - and, just as importantly, what they&apos;re wearing.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45555734</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:49:51 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Tariq Ramadan: #MeToo in the Muslim world</Title>
            <Description>Several women have now come forward to accuse Tariq Ramadan, one of the Muslim world’s most famous thinkers, of sexual assault.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45552139</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:35:09 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;Drug dealers only&apos; parking space highlights London crime</Title>
            <Description>Residents in an east London neighbourhood, near Shoreditch, want to highlight drug crime in the area.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-london-45557730</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 09:27:54 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Japan billionaire to be first moon tourist</Title>
            <Description>The first private passenger to fly around the Moon with SpaceX will be a Japanese billionaire.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-45550755</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 08:57:41 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Paper review: Brexit &apos;darkest hour&apos; alarm and savings rate &apos;rip-off&apos;</Title>
            <Description>A range of stories are on Tuesday&apos;s front pages, including Brexit and low interest rates for savers.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/blogs-the-papers-45555575</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 04:34:25 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The 107-year-old who fought fires during the Blitz</Title>
            <Description>The story of the 107-year-old who was among the first to tackle the fires in London World War Two.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-sussex-45402305</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:29:53 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>First-date peach tree bears fruit for son</Title>
            <Description>Rhys O&apos;Neill&apos;s promise to his girlfriend stood the test of time - as their son discovered.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45552572</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 18:21:13 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Baby squirrels freed from tail tangle in Wisconsin</Title>
            <Description>Five squirrel siblings are saved by a US wildlife centre after their tails got dangerously tangled.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45545179</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 18:34:59 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Chowberry app prevents food waste in Nigeria</Title>
            <Description>Oscar Ekponimo&apos;s mobile app Chowberry connects people to supermarket food that would ordinarily end up in the bin.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-44852495</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:54:20 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>D-Day veteran Harry Read, 94, skydives for first time since WW2</Title>
            <Description>The last time 94-year-old Harry Read jumped from a plane he was over Normandy in 1944.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-dorset-45551505</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 14:01:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Dad asks: &apos;When did eyebrows become so important?&apos; and rant goes viral</Title>
            <Description>Fifteen million people have joined comedian Gary Meikle&apos;s campaign against the current eyebrow obsession.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-45547076</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 11:55:35 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;I dialled into work and prayed my baby wouldn&apos;t wake up&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Winning flexible working hours can bring a new set of major problems, a survey finds.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45484904</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:12:25 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The man who has performed 23,000 post-mortems</Title>
            <Description>Dr Richard Shepherd has examined evidence from 9/11 and 7/7 terror attacks, and the death of Stephen Lawrence.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-45548977</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:10:37 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>School open days: Eight things to look for</Title>
            <Description>Glossy prospectuses and slick open evenings, but what should I look for when visiting secondary schools?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/education-41469041</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:28:27 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>South Korea&apos;s Moon Jae-in: Caught between Trump and Kim</Title>
            <Description>South Korea&apos;s Moon Jae-in, making a high-pressure trip to the North, faces a series of challenges.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-45543956</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:23:15 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The rise of the payment app: &apos;I hardly use cash any more&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Person-to-person payment apps are rising fast in popularity around the world, but are they safe?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45515666</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:48:49 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Last call for Nevada’s brothels?</Title>
            <Description>Brothels have been legal in Nevada since 1971 - but could they face the axe?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45486174</URL>
            <Date>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 23:12:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Billy Joe Saunders: World champion boxer charged with misconduct over &apos;sickening&apos; social media video</Title>
            <Description>British world champion Billy Joe Saunders is charged with misconduct by the British Boxing Board of Control over a social media video described as &quot;sickening&quot;.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/boxing/45561101</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:56:15 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Champions League: Liverpool v PSG - Why Kylian Mbappe is the real deal</Title>
            <Description>On the eve of Paris St-Germain&apos;s Champions League match against Liverpool, BBC football analyst Pat Nevin looks at the reasons why France&apos;s World Cup star Kylian Mbappe could become the best player in the world.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45542009</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:31:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Sam Burgess &apos;happy for truth to be found&apos; as he addresses sexting allegations</Title>
            <Description>England international Sam Burgess is &quot;happy for the truth to be found&quot; following allegations his social media account was used to send lewd pictures to a woman in May.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/rugby-league/45557624</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 06:53:52 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Champions League is back: The best games to watch this week</Title>
            <Description>BBC Sport looks at some of the most intriguing fixtures in the opening group games of the 2018-19 Champions League.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45522544</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 06:13:23 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>What British people think about Brexit now</Title>
            <Description>With six months to go until Brexit, opinions on the subject remain sharply divided.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45520517</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:25:26 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Speed dating Brexit-style</Title>
            <Description>Believe in Brexit at first sight? Three pairs chat about how Brexit will affect their lives.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45552140</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:31:38 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Brexit negotiations: Try our chatbot for more focus on the issues</Title>
            <Description>Questions and clear responses to the big questions about the UK&apos;s departure from the UK.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45524231</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 07:48:35 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>What a &apos;no deal&apos; means for Rotterdam</Title>
            <Description>Europe&apos;s largest port plans to employ more than 900 extra customs staff to deal with any extra checks needed.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45526207</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:34:02 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Brexit: What do French people think?</Title>
            <Description>Divorce settlements and racing off a cliff are just some of the ways the French media has given its views on Brexit.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45525645</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 10:22:13 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Brexit: All you need to know about the UK leaving the EU</Title>
            <Description>A guide to plans for the UK to leave the European Union, after the 2016 referendum.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-32810887</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 12:43:53 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Reality Check: Is the UK ready for Brexit?</Title>
            <Description>Reality Check unpacks a new report on the UK&apos;s Brexit progress.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45509582</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 06:18:35 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Reality Check: The Irish border problem</Title>
            <Description>Could the European Research Group&apos;s suggestions for the Northern Ireland border work?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-northern-ireland-45499064</URL>
            <Date>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 15:47:43 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Why is Brexit taking sooo long?</Title>
            <Description>A quick guide to Brexit and why it seems to be taking so long for the UK to leave the European Union.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-43492937</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 05:53:00 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Birmingham&apos;s Brexit concerns</Title>
            <Description>Jon Kay asks voters in Birmingham what they want to know about the UK&apos;s plans to leave the European Union.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45525625</URL>
            <Date>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 23:29:34 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Josef Frantisek: The Battle of Britain&apos;s Czech hero</Title>
            <Description>Not all the Battle of Britain pilots were British. A new film celebrates the Polish 303 Squadron - and its sole Czech pilot, Josef Frantisek.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45516556</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 23:07:23 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Sir Vince Cable Lib Dem conference speech focuses on Brexit</Title>
            <Description>The Lib Dem leader will tell his party conference &quot;fundamentalists&quot; will leave the UK in economic pain.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45553411</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:39:28 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mini plant to close for a month post-Brexit</Title>
            <Description>The BMW-owned factory will shut down to avoid disruption in the event of a no-deal departure.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45561908</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:10:44 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Coventry police black males advice is &apos;inflammatory&apos;</Title>
            <Description>A message was sent to pubs and clubs about &quot;young black males intent on committing disorder&quot;.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-coventry-warwickshire-45554543</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:07:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Amanda Reid: Australian Paralympian &apos;exaggerated symptoms&apos;</Title>
            <Description>A former coach and other athletes tell the BBC of suspicions about Paralympic athlete Amanda Reid.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-australia-45553010</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:09:28 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Regret over shaming homeless man filmed shaving on train</Title>
            <Description>A viral video of a man shaving on the train has got people questioning if we should be so quick to shame people online</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/blogs-trending-45558344</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:59:29 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Emmy Awards 2018: Matthew Rhys surprises fans with accent</Title>
            <Description>Welsh actor Matthew Rhys surprised fans when he accepted his Emmy award in his native accent.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45559664</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:15:46 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The Emmy-winning TV shows you may never have heard of</Title>
            <Description>These are the TV series that won big at the Emmys but haven&apos;t really made an impact in the UK.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45559974</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:37:03 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Ben Stokes and Alex Hales charged with bringing game into disrepute</Title>
            <Description>Ben Stokes and Alex Hales are charged with bringing the game into disrepute by the ECB following an incident outside a Bristol nightclub.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/cricket/45561380</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:33:34 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Benfica thrash Ponte de Frielas 28-0</Title>
            <Description>Watch as Benfica thrash Ponte de Frielas 28-0 as they made their debut in the second division of the Portuguese women&apos;s league.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45550697</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 05:14:26 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Enzo Calzaghe: Boxing loses giant in champion trainer</Title>
            <Description>BBC Sport Wales&apos; Michael Pearlman pays tribute to boxing trainer Enzo Calzaghe following his death at the age of 69.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/wales/45559654</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:56:32 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Scissors, single-markets and subsidies: Brexit in the hairdressers</Title>
            <Description>A remainer cuts a leaver&apos;s hair, and vice-versa - can they get along?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45561887</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:37:46 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Israel blames Syria for Russian aircrew deaths but &apos;expresses sorrow&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Fifteen personnel died when an aircraft was downed by Syrian fire after Israel launched an air raid.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45563304</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:42:03 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Woodcote ram-raiders escape with stolen Lambrini</Title>
            <Description>Four men who twice smashed their way into a Co-op were unable to remove a cash machine.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-oxfordshire-45561404</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:12:06 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BMW to shut Mini plant for month after Brexit</Title>
            <Description>The BMW-owned factory will shut down to avoid potential disruption in case of a no-deal departure.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45561908</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:47:35 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;How breastfeeding on mountain race made me go viral&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Sophie Power was pictured breastfeeding during a gruelling 106-mile race at Mont Blanc.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-45562017</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:26:10 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Westminster inquest: Security &apos;completely failed&apos; stabbed PC</Title>
            <Description>An opportunity to save Keith Palmer&apos;s life was possibly lost, a firearms officer tells an inquest.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45564224</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:07:02 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>No-deal Brexit &apos;could make policing harder&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Loss of the EU Arrest Warrant could make cases like the Novichok attack investigation harder, a police chief says.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45561527</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:04:34 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Sir Vince Cable: Brexit not inevitable and must be stopped</Title>
            <Description>The Lib Dem leader says Brexit &quot;can and must be stopped&quot; in his big party conference speech.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45553411</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:43:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Coventry bus crash: Kailash Chander was driving dangerously</Title>
            <Description>Kailash Chander was diagnosed with dementia after a crash which left two dead, a court is told.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-coventry-warwickshire-45561937</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:15:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>NFL: Chicago Bears defence dominates Russell Wilson&apos;s Seattle Seahawks</Title>
            <Description>The Chicago Bears defence puts in a dominant performance to overwhelm Russell Wilson&apos;s Seattle Seahawks and secure their first win of the season in a 24-17 victory on Monday night.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/american-football/45559494</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 08:48:48 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>UK visas: High-skilled migrants cap &apos;should be scrapped&apos;</Title>
            <Description>A key report suggests making it easier for skilled workers from anywhere in the world to come to the UK after Brexit.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45556246</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 18:17:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Russian aircrew deaths: Putin and Netanyahu defuse tension</Title>
            <Description>Fifteen personnel died when an aircraft was downed by Syrian fire after Israel launched an air raid.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45563304</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:55:29 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Chemnitz unrest: German top spy Maassen forced out</Title>
            <Description>Germany&apos;s domestic intelligence chief is moved to another post amid a row over far-right violence.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45546012</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:29:50 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The heartbreaking photo that raised $43,000 in one day</Title>
            <Description>Indians were moved by the photo of the son of a sewer worker grieving next to his father&apos;s body.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-india-45559394</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:02:10 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>China hits back at Trump with tariffs on $60bn of US goods</Title>
            <Description>The measures come after the US imposed tariffs on $200bn of Chinese imports.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45555749</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:55:09 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Boy dresses like Black Panther hero &apos;to feel like himself&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Stephanie Hardy&apos;s son is picked on at school for his size but his confidence was boosted at a Comic Expo event.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45565444</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:26:23 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;Supermodel&apos; Chloe wins film role and fulfils fashion dream</Title>
            <Description>The little girl who captured hearts with her &quot;wear odd socks&quot; video has beaten non-disability actors to a film role.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-glasgow-west-45560004</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:46:05 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Personality tests: Are you average, self-centred, role-model or reserved?</Title>
            <Description>Researchers identify four new types after studying the results of more than one million people.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45561194</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:33:54 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>London Fashion Week: Representation is &apos;still a problem&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Strides have been made towards diversity on London&apos;s catwalks but is it enough?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45548825</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:51:09 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Barcelona 4-0 PSV Eindhoven: Lionel Messi scores hat-trick in Champions League win</Title>
            <Description>Lionel Messi scores a hat-trick as Barcelona thrash Dutch champions PSV Eindhoven in their opening Champions League game.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45566374</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 18:52:52 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Inter Milan 0-1 Tottenham Hotspur: Inter stun Spurs with late fightback</Title>
            <Description>Late goals from Mauro Icardi and Matias Vecino stun Tottenham as Inter Milan celebrate their return to the Champions League with a dramatic win at the San Siro.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45551705</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 18:56:52 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
    </Entrys>
</root>
