<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
    <Entrys>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hurricane Florence: Life-threatening storm to soon hit North Carolina</Title>
            <Description>Officials warn Hurricane Florence could kill &quot;a lot of people&quot; as it nears the US East Coast.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45517260</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:27:03 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Prison staff protesting over inmate violence - POA union</Title>
            <Description>Protests are being held at &quot;the majority&quot; of prisons, but the government says the action is illegal.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45518744</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:34:58 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lehman anniversary: The five most surprising consequences</Title>
            <Description>A decade on, some of the big consequences of the financial crisis are also the most surprising.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45478670</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 21:53:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Westminster inquest: Court shown moment PC Keith Palmer stabbed</Title>
            <Description>&quot;Distressing&quot; footage is shown in court of the moment he was stabbed during the 2017 Westminster attack.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45522294</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:45:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Skripal Novichok poising: RT editor hangs up on Newsnight</Title>
            <Description>The journalist who interviewed the suspects in the Novichok attack took offence at Kirsty Wark&apos;s question.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45517388</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 02:11:33 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Ex-JLS member Oritse Williams charged with Wolverhampton rape</Title>
            <Description>Oritse Williams, 31, allegedly raped a fan in a hotel room after a concert in 2016.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-birmingham-45518544</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 08:10:08 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kimora Zondo, 7, died after hood caught on door</Title>
            <Description>There is &quot;no evidence&quot; of how Kimora Zondo became caught after reconstructions ruled out possibilities.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45519785</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:40:18 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lee Rigby: Fundraiser Gary Gardner jailed for fraud</Title>
            <Description>Lee Rigby&apos;s family said they &quot;never received a penny from&quot; Gary Gardner.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-leicestershire-45522484</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:52:35 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Wetherspoons warns of pricier pints</Title>
            <Description>Pub chain reports record sales and profits but says its rock-bottom prices are likely to rise.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45518774</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 07:26:00 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Brexit: Bank chief makes property crash warning</Title>
            <Description>Bank of England governor Mark Carney tells the cabinet a no-deal Brexit could see home prices plunge.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45516678</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:06:51 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hundreds stranded on new high-speed train in Devon</Title>
            <Description>Passengers had to be evacuated from the Hitachi 800 after it broke down in Devon.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-cornwall-45519014</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:01:39 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Super Typhoon Mangkhut: &apos;People tying down roofs&apos;</Title>
            <Description>People in the Philippines are preparing for the worst as Typhoon Mangkhut powers towards them.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-45518464</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 06:34:36 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Big Brother and Celebrity Big Brother are officially ending</Title>
            <Description>Show makers announced on Friday that the 19th series of the Channel 5 show would be its last.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45519752</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:56:15 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The Papers: Russia&apos;s &apos;insult&apos; and Carney&apos;s warning</Title>
            <Description>An &quot;extraordinary&quot; interview on Russian TV and a Bank of England Brexit briefing make the front pages.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/blogs-the-papers-45517066</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 05:04:42 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Uranus Examiner: Local newspaper stirs controversy</Title>
            <Description>An unusually named town in Missouri is stirring controversy with the title of its new newspaper.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45519884</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:46:50 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Quiz of the Week: Who sang Naomi to victory?</Title>
            <Description>It&apos;s the weekly news quiz - have you been paying attention to what&apos;s been going on in the world over the past seven days?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45511452</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:40:24 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nottingham make-up artist&apos;s surreal work is Instagram hit</Title>
            <Description>Romanie Jade-Tulloch&apos;s mind-bending artworks can take five hours to create.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-nottinghamshire-45514535</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:23:48 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The Skripal suspects&apos; walk through Salisbury</Title>
            <Description>Two suspects in the poisoning of a Russian ex-spy in the UK have said they were merely tourists.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45515013</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:03:15 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nintendo announces raft of new games for Switch console</Title>
            <Description>The Japanese firm announces a range of new games for its console - as well as a new retro controller.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-45520504</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:28:09 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Reviving Italy&apos;s ghost towns with an unusual hotel</Title>
            <Description>An unusual hotel, scattered throughout the community, is breathing life back into deserted villages.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-45437803</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:41:13 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Being 18 on UK&apos;s Rathlin Island</Title>
            <Description>Benedict Anslow talks about what life is like as one of the few young people on Rathlin Island.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-northern-ireland-45500374</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:50:50 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Schoolboy crush pair wed in Leicestershire 60 years later</Title>
            <Description>Eric and Elaine Bogliani marry in the classroom where they met aged seven and nine.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-leicestershire-45514533</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:58:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC News Channel</Title>
            <Description>BBC coverage of latest developments</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10318089</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:55:21 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Why Afghanistan is more dangerous than ever</Title>
            <Description>The Taliban are mounting deadly attacks across Afghanistan, and the 17-year war has no clear end in sight.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-45507560</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:21:56 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The first lady of Jacobean Sex Comedy</Title>
            <Description>Funny and Forgotten: How history ignored the first lady of rom-com.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45433726</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:12:41 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Facebook UK boss: We want to give users more control</Title>
            <Description>Steve Hatch says Facebook could do a &quot;much better job&quot; of helping users control their experience.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45516746</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 20:14:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>From Mars Bars to Thunderbirds: Eight things Slough gave the world</Title>
            <Description>Slough received its Royal Charter 80 years ago - but what has the Berkshire town given to the world?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-berkshire-45420755</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:25:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Crowdfunded cancer treatments - do they work?</Title>
            <Description>Experts are concerned vulnerable patients are being exploited.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-45509942</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 07:50:50 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hurricane Florence: Four reasons to fear this storm</Title>
            <Description>Why it couldn&apos;t hit a worse area in the US</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45504866</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 22:42:00 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Crazy Rich Asians: Henry Golding on becoming a leading man in his first film</Title>
            <Description>Henry Golding on how it feels to swap being a journalist for a film star.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45498674</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 01:38:27 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>‘Why I filmed a man take his final breath&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Documentary maker Steven Eastwood says he filmed four terminally ill people to explore the reality of death.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45483616</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:45:53 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Can the city of pizza reinvent itself as a tech capital?</Title>
            <Description>How a city best known for pizza, football and crime is embracing tech to revive its fortunes.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45486674</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:16:40 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>French heritage lottery aims to save national treasures</Title>
            <Description>France&apos;s new lottery is raising money for hundreds of historic buildings - borrowing a British idea.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45509572</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:16:00 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Singapore GP: Daniel Ricciardo fastest as Charles Leclerc hits wall</Title>
            <Description>Daniel Ricciardo is fastest in Singapore GP first practice as Kimi Raikkonen&apos;s Ferrari replacement Charles Leclerc crashes into a wall.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/formula1/45519704</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:40:14 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Romelu Lukaku: Man Utd boss Jose Mourinho &apos;does not fake emotions&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Manchester United striker Romelu Lukaku tells BBC Sport about &quot;real&quot; manager Jose Mourinho and being schooled by Didier Drogba and Thierry Henry.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45516847</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:06:20 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Serena Williams: Jamie Murray says men do not get preferential treatment</Title>
            <Description>Jamie Murray says claims men are treated more leniently than women by tennis umpires is &quot;a bit far-fetched&quot;.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/tennis/45513038</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 18:58:36 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Dawid Godziek land&apos;s first quadruple tail whip on a mountain bike</Title>
            <Description>Watch Polish rider Dawid Godziek land the world&apos;s first quadruple tail whip on a mountain bike.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/cycling/45514844</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:08:02 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Premier League predictions: Lawro v actor Mark Wahlberg</Title>
            <Description>BBC Sport football pundit Mark Lawrenson takes on actor Mark Wahlberg to predict this weekend&apos;s Premier League results.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45435523</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 19:25:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Recovery and clouds on the Spanish horizon</Title>
            <Description>Ten years on from Spain&apos;s financial crisis, it&apos;s possible to see recovery and clouds on the horizon.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45485657</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:09:33 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;I lost my dream job at Lehman and now make pasta&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Natalia Rogoff lost her &quot;dream job&quot; when Lehman Brothers went bust, she then set up a pasta business.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45501476</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:10:33 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>How the financial crash provided some a new life and new hope</Title>
            <Description>Two women tell the BBC how the financial crash had a devastating but also positive impact on their lives.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45334996</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:11:28 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>How did the financial crisis affect your finances?</Title>
            <Description>A decade on, the way we deal with our personal finances has changed - but not always for good.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45483636</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 23:04:32 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Who was to blame for the financial crisis?</Title>
            <Description>BBC Business editor Simon Jack explores who could have been to blame for the global financial crisis.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45489064</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 23:19:42 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Paul McCartney on handling crowds, and why he calls Donald Trump &quot;the mad captain&quot;</Title>
            <Description>The star also says he can take the train to London without being spotted. But how?</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45482360</URL>
            <Date>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 23:58:02 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kristina Vogel on crash that left her paralysed: &apos;I&apos;ve learned it is OK to cry at how bad it is&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Double Olympic cycling champion Kristina Vogel on coming to terms with the crash that has left her paralysed.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/cycling/45503798</URL>
            <Date>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 20:47:51 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Fenella Fielding, Sixties femme fatale</Title>
            <Description>Carry On Screaming actress and &quot;England&apos;s First Lady of the double entendre&quot; dies at 90.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/45409341</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:18:48 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Skripal Novichok poisoning: RT editor hangs up on Newsnight</Title>
            <Description>The journalist who interviewed the suspects in the Novichok attack took offence at Kirsty Wark&apos;s question.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45517388</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 02:11:33 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Electoral Commission got Brexit law wrong over Vote Leave, court rules</Title>
            <Description>The Electoral Commission loses a High Court case over its policing of Vote Leave&apos;s referendum spending.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45519676</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:09:13 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC Politics Live</Title>
            <Description>Live coverage of the day&apos;s politics from Westminster.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-24618323</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 11:26:10 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Super League: Clubs vote to scrap Super 8s in favour of &apos;one up, one down&apos; system</Title>
            <Description>Rugby league clubs vote to scrap the Super 8s format and return to a conventional promotion and relegation system from 2019.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/rugby-league/45520586</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:39:04 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hurricane Florence: Life-threatening storm lands in North Carolina</Title>
            <Description>Officials warn Hurricane Florence could kill &quot;a lot of people&quot; as it hits the US East Coast.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45517260</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:58:35 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Fiona Scourfield death: Boy killed stepmum with samurai sword</Title>
            <Description>Rueben Brathwaite will serve 15 years for killing Fiona Scourfield with an axe and samurai sword.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45522338</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:02:24 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC News at One</Title>
            <Description>BBC coverage of latest developments</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10318089</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:55:21 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Fraud ringleader jailed over &apos;boiler room&apos; scam</Title>
            <Description>The ringleader of a scam designed to con 170 investors out of £2.8m has been sent to prison.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45521235</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:10:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Skripal case: Russian &apos;spies&apos; targeted Swiss lab</Title>
            <Description>Russians were reportedly caught spying on a Swiss lab involved in the Salisbury poisoning inquiry.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-45522614</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:15:27 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Prison staff protest over &apos;unprecedented&apos; inmate violence</Title>
            <Description>Officers say they face attacks by groups of prisoners, being spat at and having urine thrown at them.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45518744</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:38:11 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Boy murdered stepmum Fiona Scourfield with samurai sword</Title>
            <Description>A teenager &quot;obsessed&quot; with extreme violence tried to upload pictures of her body to the internet.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45522338</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:51:39 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>World Afro Day: ‘Why I love my natural hair’</Title>
            <Description>Women talk about why they love their natural hair.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45524065</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:44:44 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Electoral Commission &apos;misinterpreted&apos; Vote Leave expenses, court rules</Title>
            <Description>The Electoral Commission loses a High Court case over its policing of Vote Leave&apos;s referendum spending.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-45519676</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:15:55 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Trump ex-campaign chief Manafort to help Mueller inquiry in plea deal</Title>
            <Description>In a plea deal, the former Trump campaign chairman also pleads guilty to two criminal charges.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45525325</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:35:25 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>House of Fraser online customers refused refunds</Title>
            <Description>Sports Direct, the chain&apos;s new owner, says it won&apos;t give refunds for goods ordered before the takeover.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-45520194</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:49:37 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Salford fatal fire: Arson death children &apos;angels in the sky&apos;</Title>
            <Description>Mourners at the funeral of the four children hear a tribute from their mother, who could not attend.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-manchester-45519364</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:35:41 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kate Moss regrets &apos;nothing tastes as good as skinny feels&apos; comment</Title>
            <Description>Almost ten years on from the model&apos;s controversial mantra, she explains why she got it wrong.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-45522714</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:27:07 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Backlash over Arriva Trains Wales lost wallet return charge</Title>
            <Description>Adam Howells had to pay more than £10 to Arriva Trains Wales to have his wallet returned.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-45519994</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:55:38 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Maps: Where has Hurricane Florence hit?</Title>
            <Description>Satellite images, maps and graphics showing where the category one storm will hit and the impact it is expected to have.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45511312</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:31:19 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>&apos;My girl&apos;s meningitis was diagnosed as ear infection&apos;</Title>
            <Description>A charity warns the NHS must be more vigilant over deadly meningitis and sepsis cases.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-45501854</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:37:53 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>YouTube nursery-rhyme channel with billions of views sold</Title>
            <Description>The Little Baby Bum channel has racked up more than 17.5 billion views.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-45523304</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:13:36 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Maniac: Mixed reviews for Emma Stone&apos;s Netflix show</Title>
            <Description>The psychological dark comedy series stars Hollywood royalty Emma Stone and Jonah Hill.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-45519744</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 10:00:11 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Shoplifters and a law that doesn&apos;t deter them</Title>
            <Description>A shopkeeper says he is losing thousands of pounds of stock each month, as figures show arrests are falling.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-45512468</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:08:23 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Jose Mourinho: Man Utd boss defends Marcus Rashford playing time</Title>
            <Description>Manchester United boss Jose Mourinho defends his use of Marcus Rashford following claims the striker is not getting enough game time.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/45519863</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:52:01 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Singapore GP: Kimi Raikkonen top as Sebastian Vettel hits wall</Title>
            <Description>Ferrari&apos;s Kimi Raikkonen leads Lewis Hamilton&apos;s Mercedes by just 0.011 seconds in second practice at the Singapore Grand Prix.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/formula1/45522627</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:20:17 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Davis Cup 2018: Great Britain lead Uzbekistan after Dan Evans beats Denis Istomin</Title>
            <Description>Dan Evans puts Great Britain ahead in their Davis Cup tie against Uzbekistan with victory over Denis Istomin in a gripping opening singles rubber.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/tennis/45524155</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:26:58 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Typhoon Mangkhut: Philippines braces for &apos;strongest&apos; storm</Title>
            <Description>The storm, described by forecasters as the strongest this year, is set to make landfall soon.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-45517803</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:53:19 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>BBC News at Six</Title>
            <Description>BBC coverage of latest developments</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10318089</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:55:21 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Vuelta a Espana 2018: Simon Yates increases lead to over a minute after stage 19</Title>
            <Description>Simon Yates extends his lead at the Vuelta a Espana to one minute 38 seconds after finishing second in stage 19.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/cycling/45526525</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:30:27 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Manafort plea deal: Trump ex-campaign chief to help Mueller inquiry</Title>
            <Description>In a plea deal, the ex-Trump campaign chief admits two charges and will aid the Russia probe.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-45525325</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 17:07:12 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hurricanes and typhoons: How to survive a major storm</Title>
            <Description>Two huge storms are threatening people on opposite sides of the world. Here&apos;s how to cope.</Description>
            <URL>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-45521927</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:56:57 GMT</Date>
        </Entry>
    </Entrys>
</root>
