<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
    <Entrys>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Golden Gate Ventures closes new $100M fund for Southeast Asia</Title>
            <Description>Singapore&amp;#8217;s Golden Gate Ventures has announced the close of its newest (and third) fund for Southeast Asia at a total of $100 million. The fund hit a first close in the summer, as TechCrunch reported at the time, and now it has reached full capacity. Seven-year-old Golden Gate said its LPs include existing backers Singapore [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/L5xQnpvf2TA/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 01:21:29 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>A Tesla investor says he was recently questioned by US regulators about that infamous ‘funding secured’ tweet</Title>
            <Description>Last week, onstage at TechCrunch Disrupt, regulator Jina Choi, who heads the SEC&amp;#8217;s wide-reaching San Francisco unit, declined to confirm or deny that the SEC is investigating Tesla CEO Elon Musk for possible fraud. Said Choi, &amp;#8220;I can&amp;#8217;t tell you about any particular investigation in our office. And I can&amp;#8217;t confirm or deny the existence [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/ecLyOgMSnUA/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:39:31 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nintendo finally announces some new games for the Switch</Title>
            <Description>Nintendo is at last (at last!) bringing some new content to the Switch! Yes! In a Nintendo Direct, the company let fly a number of games and a couple of original titles. The biggest Nintendo-produced titles we had glimpses of are a new Animal Crossing in development for the Switch and Luigi&amp;#8217;s Mansion 3. We [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/ZhKDfOGcCRw/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:38:07 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nintendo’s NES Switch controllers activate the nostalgia centers (and wallets) of retro gamers</Title>
            <Description>The news that Nintendo would be adding NES games to the Switch as part of its paid online service had a mixed reception, but the company has completely made up for this controversial decision by releasing wireless NES controllers with which to play those games. At $60 they&amp;#8217;re a bit steep, but come on. You [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/gb3ndhjvaq0/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:18:09 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The iPhone XR is the one to get</Title>
            <Description>The iPhone XR arrived like an afterthought. No surprise, really. Apple’s always been one to lead with its best foot forward — the latest, greatest and, quite literally, the largest. Projecting the life on the bleeding edge is a cornerstone of the company’s image, market share and stock price. The iPhone XR isn’t that. In [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/-jSP9wLWdtU/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 22:53:40 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Former Uber exec alleges ex-PR chief ‘destroyed his reputation’</Title>
            <Description>A nasty legal battle is set to play out between two former Uber executives. Eric Alexander, the ride-hailing company&amp;#8217;s former president of business in Asia-Pacific, has filed suit against former Uber PR chief Rachel Whetstone . Alexander blames Whetstone for his firing from Uber in June 2017, claiming her &amp;#8220;grossly misleading statements&amp;#8221; both internally at Uber and [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Zj8wVyT1YaA/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 22:00:19 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Twitch hires head of diversity and inclusion</Title>
            <Description>Twitch, the Amazon-owned streaming platform, has brought on its first head of diversity and inclusion, as well as a new chief financial officer and chief human resources officer. Katrina Jones, who will start next month as Twitch&amp;#8217;s head of diversity and inclusion, is the former head of diversity at Vimeo. At Vimeo, Jones created the [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/vliBL3wGXkI/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 21:00:30 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The second blockchain bubble is now complete — what’s next?</Title>
            <Description>The last few months haven’t been easy for crypto investors. Following the dizzying highs of crypto trading late last year, which saw Bitcoin reach a peak of $19,276 and a market cap of $323 billion and Ether reach $1,152 with a market cap of more than $112 billion, prices have crashed. Today, Bitcoin trades at [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/0axsbJgNNYQ/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 20:57:57 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The funding mirage: How to secure international investment from emerging markets</Title>
            <Description>Looking for funding as a startup in Latin America is a lot like looking for a watering hole in the middle of the desert. You know it’s out there, but finding it in time is a life or death situation.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/cVx5QjDmDUs/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 20:00:50 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>It’s the end of crypto as we know it and I feel fine</Title>
            <Description>Watching the current price madness is scary. Bitcoin is falling and rising in $500 increments with regularity and Ethereum and its attendant ICOs are in a seeming freefall with a few &amp;#8220;dead cat bounces&amp;#8221; to keep things lively. What this signals is not that crypto is dead, however. It signals that the early, elated period [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/HFseMVEigOs/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 19:55:06 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Microsoft acquires Lobe, a drag-and-drop AI tool</Title>
            <Description>Microsoft today announced that is has acquired Lobe, a startup that lets you build machine learning models with the help of a simple drag-and-drop interface. Microsoft plans to use Lobe, which only launched into beta earlier this year, to build upon its own efforts to make building AI models easier, though, for the time being, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/hDX1zLshCgU/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 19:08:00 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>This insect-inspired robot can fly a kilometer on a charge with its flappy wings</Title>
            <Description>The incredible agility of the common house or fruit fly puts every drone and robot to shame, but devices inspired by them are beginning to catch up. A new four-winged flapping robot not only successfully imitates the fruit fly&apos;s hyper-agile flying method, but can travel for up to a kilometer before running out of juice.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/NpGbb9Km7Ao/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 18:01:45 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>JBL’s smart display combines Google smarts with good sound</Title>
            <Description>If you&amp;#8217;re looking for a smart display that&amp;#8217;s powered by the Google Assistant, you now have two choices: the Lenovo Smart Display and the JBL Link View. Lenovo was first out of the gate with its surprisingly stylish gadget, but it also left room for improvement. JBL, given its heritage as an audio company, is putting [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/YSY_B6sdrAA/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:49:42 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Why rumors that Adobe could be in talks to buy Marketo make sense</Title>
            <Description>Adobe could be shopping for another piece of the digital marketing puzzle, as reports surfaced today that the company might be in talks with Vista Equity Partners to buy Marketo, a company the private equity firm purchased in May 2016 for $1.8 billion in cash. Reuters was first to report the rumor. While the report [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/JAvJenmROyg/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:31:56 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Facebook’s new ‘SapFix’ AI automatically debugs your code</Title>
            <Description>Facebook has quietly built and deployed an artificial intelligence programming tool called SapFix that scans code, automatically identifies bugs, tests different patches and suggests the best ones that engineers can choose to implement. Revealed today at Facebook&amp;#8217;s @Scale engineering conference, SapFix is already running on Facebook&amp;#8217;s massive code base and the company plans to eventually [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/L-iiMDA0JSg/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:29:59 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Online used car startup Shift raises $140 million</Title>
            <Description>Shift Technologies, an online marketplace for used cars, has closed a Series D financing round of more than $140 million in equity and debt. The round, which consists of about $70 million in debt and $71 million in equity, was led by automotive retailer Lithia Motors. Bryan DeBoer, CEO and president of Lithia, will join Shift’s [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/sEhi_HHx0dI/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:19:10 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>US lawmakers warn spy chief that ‘deep fakes’ are a national security threat</Title>
            <Description>What once sounded like science fiction is now a reality: creating almost-perfectly faked videos of people saying things they never did. Surprise: Now they&amp;#8217;re a reality, thanks to modern computing power and the power to instantly share it on the world&amp;#8217;s social stage. But U.S. lawmakers are worried that these faked videos could be used [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/bfsdeDCpjzE/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:09:11 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>OnePlus will ditch the headphone jack on its next phone</Title>
            <Description>Welp. After making a show of keeping the headphone jack around for a few extra generations, OnePlus is finally succumbing to the inevitable. The company tweeted an image of USB-C headphones and confirmed that the port will bite the dust on the upcoming 6T. “You&amp;#8217;ve got to make decisions that optimize the user experience, and [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Gcr3iIqH2jg/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:00:46 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Uber is investing $150M in Toronto to expand self-driving car efforts</Title>
            <Description>Months after an Uber self-driving vehicle struck and killed a pedestrian in Tempe, Arizona, the ride-hailing giant has announced it&apos;s adding a new engineering hub in Toronto and expanding its autonomous research team as it refocuses its self-driving car efforts.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/de4gtcjPAdw/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:50:49 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Website builder Strikingly raises $10M Series A+ to continue growth in China</Title>
            <Description>Almost exactly one year after announcing its Series A, website building platform Strikingly said today that it has raised a $10 million Series A+. The new round was led by Cathay Capital, with participation from CAS Holding, the lead investor in Strikingly’s Series A. This brings Strikingly’s total funding so far to $17.5 million. Co-founder and [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/WH-NI44pLBo/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:45:49 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The iPhone XR shows Apple admitting 3D Touch is a failure</Title>
            <Description>Remember 3D Touch? Unless you&amp;#8217;re a power iOS user you probably don&amp;#8217;t. Or, well, you&amp;#8217;d rather not. It&amp;#8217;s been clear for some time now that the technology Apple lauded at its 2015 unveiling as the &amp;#8220;next generation of multi-touch&amp;#8221; most certainly wasn&amp;#8217;t. For the mainstream iPhone user it&amp;#8217;s just that annoying thing that gets in [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/CGG-NJZsfho/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:03:50 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mobility startups: Apply to exhibit for free as a TC Top Pick at Disrupt Berlin 2018</Title>
            <Description>In the realm of rapidly evolving technologies, mobility is without doubt one of the fastest-moving. And that’s why we’re searching for up to five of the most promising early-stage mobile tech startups to apply as a TechCrunch Top Pick at Disrupt Berlin 2018 on 29-30 November. Whether you’re focused on drones, autonomous vehicles, sensors, apps, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/YaTNoMz_-08/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 08:00:35 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>DC Comics’ streaming service launches tomorrow</Title>
            <Description>Tomorrow is apparently Batman Day. That mostly means promotions from the folks at DC Entertainment and the long-awaited launch of the company’s DC Universe streaming service. If nothing else, the site is an interesting mix of multimedia content in a world of video-only sites, including original series, older content and digital comics. Users who signed [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/lGYNPv-CZbs/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:57:51 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mary Meeker, author of the Internet Trends Report, is leaving Kleiner Perkins</Title>
            <Description>Mary Meeker is leaving Kleiner Perkins to build a new fund and she&apos;s taking the firm&apos;s growth team with her, as first reported by Recode. Meeker, widely known for her annual Internet Trends Report, joined the firm in 2010 after two decades as a managing director at Morgan Stanley. She was well-established as a tech analyst on Wall Street. In Silicon Valley, she quickly built a reputation as one of the best.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/OcNkNZXuFq4/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:51:26 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Cryptocurrency mining attacks using leaked NSA hacking tools are still highly active a year later</Title>
            <Description>It&amp;#8217;s been over a year since highly classified exploits built by the National Security Agency were stolen and published online. One of the tools, dubbed EternalBlue, can covertly break into almost any Windows machine around the world. It didn&amp;#8217;t take long for hackers to start using the exploits to run ransomware on thousands of computers, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/jYuGWEB7fH8/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:30:16 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kegel trainer startup Elvie is launching a smaller, smarter, hands-free breast pump</Title>
            <Description>Elvie, a Berlin-based startup known best for its connected Kegel trainer, is jumping into the breast pump business with a new $480 hands-free system you can slip into your bra. Even with all the innovation in baby gear, breast pumps have mostly sucked (pun intended) for new moms for the past half a century. My [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/BKmAxt7uL_M/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:00:58 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lyft hires yet another ex-Tesla employee</Title>
            <Description>Lyft is on a bit of a Tesla poaching spree while Tesla employees are exiting in droves. The latest ex-Tesla employee to join Lyft is Cal Lankton, who most recently led the development of Tesla&amp;#8217;s electric vehicle charging network up until May. At Lyft, Lankton will serve as VP of infrastructure operations where he will [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/yXr7DFMJqrs/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:00:17 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Announcing the agenda for TC Sessions: AR/VR in LA on October 18</Title>
            <Description>TechCrunch is heading to UCLA on October 18 and we&amp;#8217;ve assembled some of the AR/VR industry&amp;#8217;s most prescient founders, investors and executives to chat about the startups and trends driving virtual and augmented reality in 2018. The world&amp;#8217;s top tech companies have heavily invested in AR/VR and are persistent in broadcasting the technologies&amp;#8217; potential to blur [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/xqAConye__c/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:00:10 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Amazon’s HQ2 location will be announced this year</Title>
            <Description>Things have been pretty quiet on the Amazon HQ2 front. Earlier this year, the online retail giant announced that it had whittled the list of potential host cities for a second headquarters down to 20, but beyond that, the company hasn’t shared much. Looks like we’ll be getting an answer before end of year, however. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Lot2zlfS1SU/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:59:35 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>3DHubs, once a community 3D printing service, is now sourcing all 3D prints internally</Title>
            <Description>3D Hubs, like MakeXYZ, was a community-based 3D printing service that let anyone with a printer sell their prints online. Founded in the heyday of the 3D printing revolution, the service let thousands of makers gather a little cash for making and mailing prints on their home 3D printers. Now, however, the company has moved [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/sG6W-HHtJ-A/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:55:06 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Streaming service CBS All Access rolls out support for offline viewing</Title>
            <Description>CBS All Access, the network&amp;#8217;s over-the-top streaming service for cord cutters, will now let subscribers save shows for offline viewing. The feature, &amp;#8220;Download &amp;#38; Play,&amp;#8221; is only available to those on CBS&amp;#8217;s Commercial Free plan, not those on the cheaper, ad-supported tier. It also supports a range of programming, including CBS All Access Originals, reality [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/WAwSnoDBJTQ/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:37:57 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mercedes-Benz turns to SoundHound for in-vehicle voice assistant</Title>
            <Description>Drivers of new Mercedes-Benz A-Class vehicles will soon be able to talk to their cars. And the cars will respond. Ask the car to turn on the heads-up display or for sports scores. Say you&amp;#8217;re hungry and it will suggest restaurants. The new in-vehicle assistant utilizes local and cloud data to provide drivers plenty to [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/SCGr00MaeFI/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:00:10 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Watch this robot fly like a real insect</Title>
            <Description>The DelFly is a super light, super agile robot that flies like a real insect. By using a quad-wing flapping system, this odd little bot can flit, hover, and land like a fruit fly. Part of a research project at the Delft University of Technology, this is the latest version of the DelFly and it [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/t6N5X1-2www/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:30:50 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Netflix’s newest program certifies post-production tools for Netflix Originals</Title>
            <Description>Netflix on Thursday announced a new program aimed at helping Netflix Originals artists and producers select the right tools for delivering their content to its streaming service. With the launch of the Netflix Post Technology Alliance, as the program is called, Netflix will now identify products from vendors that meet technical and delivery specifications today, and [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/iKD-KlR3Y-E/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:26:04 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Crypto’s second bubble, Juul has 60 days and three Chinese IPOs</Title>
            <Description>Hello and welcome back to Equity, TechCrunch’s venture capital-focused podcast where we unpack the numbers behind the headlines. After a long run of having guests climb aboard each week, we took a pause on that front, bringing together three of our regular hosts instead: Connie Loizos, Danny Chrichton, and myself. Despite the fact that there were [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/BxTFb0H9YE8/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:10:14 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mobile bank Chime picks up credit score improvement service Pinch in all-stock deal</Title>
            <Description>Chime, the no-fees mobile bank valued at $500 million as of its last round, has put some of its funds to use with its first acquisition. The deal is for Pinch, a startup that was focused on helping millennials and other young adults build better credit. It was best known for a service called PinchRent, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/MqWql8uvO8g/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 17:03:05 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
    </Entrys>
</root>
