<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
    <Entrys>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Teikametrics raises $10M to optimize Amazon ads</Title>
            <Description>Teikametrics is a Boston-based startup that helps retailers tackle the challenges of advertising on Amazon. Today, the company is announcing that it has raised $10 million in Series A funding. CEO Alasdair McLean-Foreman said third-party sellers represent 60 percent of the transactions on Amazon. But they don&amp;#8217;t have any real data science capabilities, so they [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/rCG29_9Bva0/</URL>
            <Date>16:16 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Metrc, whose tracing system helps regulators track cannabis from seed to sale, just raised $50 million, including from Tiger Global</Title>
            <Description>A growing number of states has legalized retail marijuana sales, but ensuring that everything works as advertised is no easy task. Among the many things that regulators have to concern themselves with are: granting licenses to dispensaries, retail sales, delivery, distribution, ensuring marijuana has been tested for pesticides and other materials, and other parts of [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/zTVXvG3HcGY/</URL>
            <Date>16:11 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>YouTube is closing the gap with Twitch on live streaming, report finds</Title>
            <Description>Twitch continues to dominate the live streaming market, with approximately 2.5 billion hours watched by viewers in the third quarter of 2018, according to a new industry report out this morning. While YouTube still trails, it&amp;#8217;s begun to close the gap with Twitch, it appears. YouTube&amp;#8217;s live streaming platform, YouTube Live, started the year with [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/yCJB1Bhile0/</URL>
            <Date>15:53 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Confirmed: ShopRunner acquires Spring, raises $40M</Title>
            <Description>ShopRunner has raised $40 million and confirmed its acquisition of ecommerce marketplace Spring.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/_BDvwHafu7c/</URL>
            <Date>15:04 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Google Maps takes on Facebook Pages with new ‘Follow’ feature for tracking businesses</Title>
            <Description>Google Maps has been steadily rolling out new features to make its app more than just a way to find places and navigate to them. In recent months, it&amp;#8217;s added things like group trip planning, music controls, commuter tools, ETA sharing, personalized recommendations, and more. Now, it&amp;#8217;s introducing a new way for users to follow their [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Ly6C5jtSCkA/</URL>
            <Date>14:59 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Palm’s tiny secondary smartphone arrives November 2</Title>
            <Description>Can’t wait to get your giant hand on Palm’s tiny “ultra-mobile?” Turns out it will be arriving sooner than later — next Friday, in fact. Verizon (you know, the giant telecom that owns the media conglomerate that owns TechCrunch) announced today that it will be launching the strange new thing on November 2. The 3.3-inch [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/JSDTzVWNAqk/</URL>
            <Date>14:44 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Cheddar buys a user-generated content biz, Rate My Professors, from Viacom</Title>
            <Description>Streaming news company Cheddar announced this morning it&amp;#8217;s acquiring Rate My Professors, the Viacom-owned site where students go online to rate and review their professors and schools across the U.S. The site, founded in 1999, has become something of a staple on the web, and by its nature it attracts the young demographic that Cheddar [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/KIAShsZ2S8Y/</URL>
            <Date>14:16 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>New plans aim to deploy the first US quantum network from Boston to Washington, DC</Title>
            <Description>About 800 kilometers of unused fiber optic cable running down the U.S. eastern seaboard is set to become the first stateside quantum network. The aim is to get the quantum network up and running and accepting customers by the end of the year, making it the first time that quantum keys will be exchanged commercially [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/IawYWzA-2sU/</URL>
            <Date>14:08 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>One-year-old Ribbon raises $225M to remove the biggest stress of home buying</Title>
            <Description>Big problems require big war chests. Ribbon wants the biggest chest of them all. The startup, which was founded just about a year ago by ex-LendingClub head of strategic development Shaival Shah and ex-Twitter/TellApart engineer Jian Wei Gan (who, full disclosure, is married to TechCrunch columnist Joyce Yang), wants to replace the incredible stress of [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/cIZWyYNBsbw/</URL>
            <Date>14:0 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>China to Trump: Dump the iPhone for a Huawei</Title>
            <Description>A China foreign ministry spokeswoman Hua Chunying dismissed yesterday’s damning report about spying on Trump’s unsecured iPhone, calling it, “fake news,” according to The South China Morning Post. She had a few other choice words for the president, suggesting he switch to a Huawei handset, or, failing that, just stop communicating. The shade amounts to [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/XEg5dLxyFY4/</URL>
            <Date>13:50 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Google Lens comes to Google Images for searching – and shopping – inside photos</Title>
            <Description>Google this morning announced it&amp;#8217;s bringing its A.I.-powered Lens technology to Google Image Search. The idea, explains the company, is to allow web searchers to learn more about what&amp;#8217;s in a photo &amp;#8211; including, in particular, items they may want to shop for and buy. For example, a photo of a well-decorated living room might [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Tks6Q72mItg/</URL>
            <Date>13:31 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Summersalt raises $6M for its direct-to-consumer line of eco-friendly swimsuits</Title>
            <Description>Founders Fund has led the $6 million Series A for the startup, which plans to use the investment to launch a line of travel apparel.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/qzzhLXgT6O4/</URL>
            <Date>13:0 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Europe’s parliament calls for full audit of Facebook in wake of breach scandal</Title>
            <Description>The European Parliament has called for a full audit of Facebook following a string of data breach scandals &amp;#8212;  including the Cambridge Analytica affair. MEPs are urging the company to allow European Union bodies to carry out a full audit to assess data protection and security of users’ personal data, following the scandal in which [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/IDZITXKEN9M/</URL>
            <Date>12:49 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Xiaomi opts for sliding camera and no notch for new bezel-less Mi Mix phone</Title>
            <Description>Xiaomi has announced the newest version of its bezel-less Mi Mix family, and it doesn&amp;#8217;t sport a notch like its Mi 8 flagship. Indeed, unlike the Mi 8 &amp;#8212; which I called one of Xiaomi&amp;#8217;s most brazen Apple clones &amp;#8212; there&amp;#8217;s a lot more to get excited about. The Mi Mix 3 was unveiled at an [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/37Q9Jc0TVn0/</URL>
            <Date>12:31 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Real estate upstart Compass acquires part of shopping app Spring, including 20+ engineers and CTO</Title>
            <Description>After raising $400 million in September in a round that valued it at $4.4 billion, the real estate startup Compass is making an acquisition to help it double down on growth: it is acquiring a portion of Spring, the mobile-first fashion shopping app that has raised more than $100 million since 2014, to work on [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/30WOsk7RQnk/</URL>
            <Date>12:0 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Twitter beats Wall St Q3 estimates with $758M in revenue</Title>
            <Description>Twitter came in ahead of analysts&amp;#8217; financial estimates in its third quarter, reporting $758 million in revenue (a 29 percent year-over-year increase) and earnings per share of 21 cents. Analysts had predicted revenue of $703 million and EPS of 14 cents per share. Ad revenue was also up 29 percent, to $650 million, and Twitter [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/DJykG54hZFw/</URL>
            <Date>11:55 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Apple picks Thailand for its second retail store in Southeast Asia</Title>
            <Description>Apple continues to increase its efforts in Southeast Asia&amp;#8217;s fast-growing market after it picked Thailand as the location for its second Apple Store in the region. A post on Apple&amp;#8217;s website reveals that it will operate a retail store at the soon-to-open Iconsiam which is set to become Bangkok&amp;#8217;s largest mall when it opens next [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/QtIv-dHvAGk/</URL>
            <Date>11:28 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Red Dead Redemption 2 sets the bar high for the next generation of open world games</Title>
            <Description>It&amp;#8217;s been nearly a decade since Rockstar Games introduced Red Dead Redemption, a massive open world game with a story about as reflective of American culture as the Grand Theft Auto franchise. Tomorrow, Red Dead Redemption II goes live after months of breathless speculation. And yes, it&amp;#8217;s as good as you dreamed it. That&amp;#8217;s not [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/GAaNGs6GfVM/</URL>
            <Date>11:01 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Xiaomi looks set to smash its 100M sales target for 2018</Title>
            <Description>Despite share price struggles, Xiaomi has revealed that it is on track for a record sales year which will see it easily surpass its goal of selling 100 million smartphones in 2018. Wang Xiang, the executive in charge of the Chinese firm&amp;#8217;s international business, said on Twitter that he expects to hit its 2018 100 million [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/xrys1sa8lHE/</URL>
            <Date>10:27 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>UK watchdog hands Facebook maximum £500K fine over Cambridge Analytica data breach</Title>
            <Description>The U.K. Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) has confirmed that it has hit Facebook with a maximum £500,000 ($645,000) fine around the way it mishandled user data following the Cambridge Analytica scandal earlier this year. The ICO announced its intention to hand Facebook the fine back in July and it said today that it had not changed [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/vau7nNrOyLc/</URL>
            <Date>9:12 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
    </Entrys>
</root>
