<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
    <Entrys>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Golden Gate Ventures closes new $100M fund for Southeast Asia</Title>
            <Description>Singapore&amp;#8217;s Golden Gate Ventures has announced the close of its newest (and third) fund for Southeast Asia at a total of $100 million. The fund hit a first close in the summer, as TechCrunch reported at the time, and now it has reached full capacity. Seven-year-old Golden Gate said its LPs include existing backers Singapore [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/L5xQnpvf2TA/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 01:21:29 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>A Tesla investor says he was recently questioned by US regulators about that infamous ‘funding secured’ tweet</Title>
            <Description>Last week, onstage at TechCrunch Disrupt, regulator Jina Choi, who heads the SEC&amp;#8217;s wide-reaching San Francisco unit, declined to confirm or deny that the SEC is investigating Tesla CEO Elon Musk for possible fraud. Said Choi, &amp;#8220;I can&amp;#8217;t tell you about any particular investigation in our office. And I can&amp;#8217;t confirm or deny the existence [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/ecLyOgMSnUA/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:39:31 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nintendo finally announces some new games for the Switch</Title>
            <Description>Nintendo is at last (at last!) bringing some new content to the Switch! Yes! In a Nintendo Direct, the company let fly a number of games and a couple of original titles. The biggest Nintendo-produced titles we had glimpses of are a new Animal Crossing in development for the Switch and Luigi&amp;#8217;s Mansion 3. We [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/ZhKDfOGcCRw/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:38:07 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nintendo’s NES Switch controllers activate the nostalgia centers (and wallets) of retro gamers</Title>
            <Description>The news that Nintendo would be adding NES games to the Switch as part of its paid online service had a mixed reception, but the company has completely made up for this controversial decision by releasing wireless NES controllers with which to play those games. At $60 they&amp;#8217;re a bit steep, but come on. You [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/gb3ndhjvaq0/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 23:18:09 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The iPhone XR is the one to get</Title>
            <Description>The iPhone XR arrived like an afterthought. No surprise, really. Apple’s always been one to lead with its best foot forward — the latest, greatest and, quite literally, the largest. Projecting the life on the bleeding edge is a cornerstone of the company’s image, market share and stock price. The iPhone XR isn’t that. In [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/-jSP9wLWdtU/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 22:53:40 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Former Uber exec alleges ex-PR chief ‘destroyed his reputation’</Title>
            <Description>A nasty legal battle is set to play out between two former Uber executives. Eric Alexander, the ride-hailing company&amp;#8217;s former president of business in Asia-Pacific, has filed suit against former Uber PR chief Rachel Whetstone . Alexander blames Whetstone for his firing from Uber in June 2017, claiming her &amp;#8220;grossly misleading statements&amp;#8221; both internally at Uber and [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Zj8wVyT1YaA/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 22:00:19 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Twitch hires head of diversity and inclusion</Title>
            <Description>Twitch, the Amazon-owned streaming platform, has brought on its first head of diversity and inclusion, as well as a new chief financial officer and chief human resources officer. Katrina Jones, who will start next month as Twitch&amp;#8217;s head of diversity and inclusion, is the former head of diversity at Vimeo. At Vimeo, Jones created the [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/vliBL3wGXkI/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 21:00:30 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The second blockchain bubble is now complete — what’s next?</Title>
            <Description>The last few months haven’t been easy for crypto investors. Following the dizzying highs of crypto trading late last year, which saw Bitcoin reach a peak of $19,276 and a market cap of $323 billion and Ether reach $1,152 with a market cap of more than $112 billion, prices have crashed. Today, Bitcoin trades at [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/0axsbJgNNYQ/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 20:57:57 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The funding mirage: How to secure international investment from emerging markets</Title>
            <Description>Looking for funding as a startup in Latin America is a lot like looking for a watering hole in the middle of the desert. You know it’s out there, but finding it in time is a life or death situation.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/cVx5QjDmDUs/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 20:00:50 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>It’s the end of crypto as we know it and I feel fine</Title>
            <Description>Watching the current price madness is scary. Bitcoin is falling and rising in $500 increments with regularity and Ethereum and its attendant ICOs are in a seeming freefall with a few &amp;#8220;dead cat bounces&amp;#8221; to keep things lively. What this signals is not that crypto is dead, however. It signals that the early, elated period [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/HFseMVEigOs/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 19:55:06 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Microsoft acquires Lobe, a drag-and-drop AI tool</Title>
            <Description>Microsoft today announced that is has acquired Lobe, a startup that lets you build machine learning models with the help of a simple drag-and-drop interface. Microsoft plans to use Lobe, which only launched into beta earlier this year, to build upon its own efforts to make building AI models easier, though, for the time being, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/hDX1zLshCgU/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 19:08:00 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>This insect-inspired robot can fly a kilometer on a charge with its flappy wings</Title>
            <Description>The incredible agility of the common house or fruit fly puts every drone and robot to shame, but devices inspired by them are beginning to catch up. A new four-winged flapping robot not only successfully imitates the fruit fly&apos;s hyper-agile flying method, but can travel for up to a kilometer before running out of juice.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/NpGbb9Km7Ao/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 18:01:45 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>JBL’s smart display combines Google smarts with good sound</Title>
            <Description>If you&amp;#8217;re looking for a smart display that&amp;#8217;s powered by the Google Assistant, you now have two choices: the Lenovo Smart Display and the JBL Link View. Lenovo was first out of the gate with its surprisingly stylish gadget, but it also left room for improvement. JBL, given its heritage as an audio company, is putting [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/YSY_B6sdrAA/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:49:42 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Why rumors that Adobe could be in talks to buy Marketo make sense</Title>
            <Description>Adobe could be shopping for another piece of the digital marketing puzzle, as reports surfaced today that the company might be in talks with Vista Equity Partners to buy Marketo, a company the private equity firm purchased in May 2016 for $1.8 billion in cash. Reuters was first to report the rumor. While the report [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/JAvJenmROyg/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:31:56 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Facebook’s new ‘SapFix’ AI automatically debugs your code</Title>
            <Description>Facebook has quietly built and deployed an artificial intelligence programming tool called SapFix that scans code, automatically identifies bugs, tests different patches and suggests the best ones that engineers can choose to implement. Revealed today at Facebook&amp;#8217;s @Scale engineering conference, SapFix is already running on Facebook&amp;#8217;s massive code base and the company plans to eventually [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/L-iiMDA0JSg/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:29:59 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Online used car startup Shift raises $140 million</Title>
            <Description>Shift Technologies, an online marketplace for used cars, has closed a Series D financing round of more than $140 million in equity and debt. The round, which consists of about $70 million in debt and $71 million in equity, was led by automotive retailer Lithia Motors. Bryan DeBoer, CEO and president of Lithia, will join Shift’s [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/sEhi_HHx0dI/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:19:10 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>US lawmakers warn spy chief that ‘deep fakes’ are a national security threat</Title>
            <Description>What once sounded like science fiction is now a reality: creating almost-perfectly faked videos of people saying things they never did. Surprise: Now they&amp;#8217;re a reality, thanks to modern computing power and the power to instantly share it on the world&amp;#8217;s social stage. But U.S. lawmakers are worried that these faked videos could be used [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/bfsdeDCpjzE/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:09:11 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>OnePlus will ditch the headphone jack on its next phone</Title>
            <Description>Welp. After making a show of keeping the headphone jack around for a few extra generations, OnePlus is finally succumbing to the inevitable. The company tweeted an image of USB-C headphones and confirmed that the port will bite the dust on the upcoming 6T. “You&amp;#8217;ve got to make decisions that optimize the user experience, and [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Gcr3iIqH2jg/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:00:46 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Uber is investing $150M in Toronto to expand self-driving car efforts</Title>
            <Description>Months after an Uber self-driving vehicle struck and killed a pedestrian in Tempe, Arizona, the ride-hailing giant has announced it&apos;s adding a new engineering hub in Toronto and expanding its autonomous research team as it refocuses its self-driving car efforts.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/de4gtcjPAdw/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:50:49 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Website builder Strikingly raises $10M Series A+ to continue growth in China</Title>
            <Description>Almost exactly one year after announcing its Series A, website building platform Strikingly said today that it has raised a $10 million Series A+. The new round was led by Cathay Capital, with participation from CAS Holding, the lead investor in Strikingly’s Series A. This brings Strikingly’s total funding so far to $17.5 million. Co-founder and [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/WH-NI44pLBo/</URL>
            <Date>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:45:49 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The iPhone XR shows Apple admitting 3D Touch is a failure</Title>
            <Description>Remember 3D Touch? Unless you&amp;#8217;re a power iOS user you probably don&amp;#8217;t. Or, well, you&amp;#8217;d rather not. It&amp;#8217;s been clear for some time now that the technology Apple lauded at its 2015 unveiling as the &amp;#8220;next generation of multi-touch&amp;#8221; most certainly wasn&amp;#8217;t. For the mainstream iPhone user it&amp;#8217;s just that annoying thing that gets in [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/CGG-NJZsfho/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:03:50 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mobility startups: Apply to exhibit for free as a TC Top Pick at Disrupt Berlin 2018</Title>
            <Description>In the realm of rapidly evolving technologies, mobility is without doubt one of the fastest-moving. And that’s why we’re searching for up to five of the most promising early-stage mobile tech startups to apply as a TechCrunch Top Pick at Disrupt Berlin 2018 on 29-30 November. Whether you’re focused on drones, autonomous vehicles, sensors, apps, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/YaTNoMz_-08/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 08:00:35 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>DC Comics’ streaming service launches tomorrow</Title>
            <Description>Tomorrow is apparently Batman Day. That mostly means promotions from the folks at DC Entertainment and the long-awaited launch of the company’s DC Universe streaming service. If nothing else, the site is an interesting mix of multimedia content in a world of video-only sites, including original series, older content and digital comics. Users who signed [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/lGYNPv-CZbs/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:57:51 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mary Meeker, author of the Internet Trends Report, is leaving Kleiner Perkins</Title>
            <Description>Mary Meeker is leaving Kleiner Perkins to build a new fund and she&apos;s taking the firm&apos;s growth team with her, as first reported by Recode. Meeker, widely known for her annual Internet Trends Report, joined the firm in 2010 after two decades as a managing director at Morgan Stanley. She was well-established as a tech analyst on Wall Street. In Silicon Valley, she quickly built a reputation as one of the best.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/OcNkNZXuFq4/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:51:26 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Cryptocurrency mining attacks using leaked NSA hacking tools are still highly active a year later</Title>
            <Description>It&amp;#8217;s been over a year since highly classified exploits built by the National Security Agency were stolen and published online. One of the tools, dubbed EternalBlue, can covertly break into almost any Windows machine around the world. It didn&amp;#8217;t take long for hackers to start using the exploits to run ransomware on thousands of computers, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/jYuGWEB7fH8/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:30:16 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Kegel trainer startup Elvie is launching a smaller, smarter, hands-free breast pump</Title>
            <Description>Elvie, a Berlin-based startup known best for its connected Kegel trainer, is jumping into the breast pump business with a new $480 hands-free system you can slip into your bra. Even with all the innovation in baby gear, breast pumps have mostly sucked (pun intended) for new moms for the past half a century. My [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/BKmAxt7uL_M/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:00:58 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lyft hires yet another ex-Tesla employee</Title>
            <Description>Lyft is on a bit of a Tesla poaching spree while Tesla employees are exiting in droves. The latest ex-Tesla employee to join Lyft is Cal Lankton, who most recently led the development of Tesla&amp;#8217;s electric vehicle charging network up until May. At Lyft, Lankton will serve as VP of infrastructure operations where he will [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/yXr7DFMJqrs/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:00:17 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Announcing the agenda for TC Sessions: AR/VR in LA on October 18</Title>
            <Description>TechCrunch is heading to UCLA on October 18 and we&amp;#8217;ve assembled some of the AR/VR industry&amp;#8217;s most prescient founders, investors and executives to chat about the startups and trends driving virtual and augmented reality in 2018. The world&amp;#8217;s top tech companies have heavily invested in AR/VR and are persistent in broadcasting the technologies&amp;#8217; potential to blur [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/xqAConye__c/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:00:10 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Amazon’s HQ2 location will be announced this year</Title>
            <Description>Things have been pretty quiet on the Amazon HQ2 front. Earlier this year, the online retail giant announced that it had whittled the list of potential host cities for a second headquarters down to 20, but beyond that, the company hasn’t shared much. Looks like we’ll be getting an answer before end of year, however. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Lot2zlfS1SU/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:59:35 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>3DHubs, once a community 3D printing service, is now sourcing all 3D prints internally</Title>
            <Description>3D Hubs, like MakeXYZ, was a community-based 3D printing service that let anyone with a printer sell their prints online. Founded in the heyday of the 3D printing revolution, the service let thousands of makers gather a little cash for making and mailing prints on their home 3D printers. Now, however, the company has moved [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/sG6W-HHtJ-A/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:55:06 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Streaming service CBS All Access rolls out support for offline viewing</Title>
            <Description>CBS All Access, the network&amp;#8217;s over-the-top streaming service for cord cutters, will now let subscribers save shows for offline viewing. The feature, &amp;#8220;Download &amp;#38; Play,&amp;#8221; is only available to those on CBS&amp;#8217;s Commercial Free plan, not those on the cheaper, ad-supported tier. It also supports a range of programming, including CBS All Access Originals, reality [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/WAwSnoDBJTQ/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:37:57 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mercedes-Benz turns to SoundHound for in-vehicle voice assistant</Title>
            <Description>Drivers of new Mercedes-Benz A-Class vehicles will soon be able to talk to their cars. And the cars will respond. Ask the car to turn on the heads-up display or for sports scores. Say you&amp;#8217;re hungry and it will suggest restaurants. The new in-vehicle assistant utilizes local and cloud data to provide drivers plenty to [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/SCGr00MaeFI/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:00:10 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Watch this robot fly like a real insect</Title>
            <Description>The DelFly is a super light, super agile robot that flies like a real insect. By using a quad-wing flapping system, this odd little bot can flit, hover, and land like a fruit fly. Part of a research project at the Delft University of Technology, this is the latest version of the DelFly and it [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/t6N5X1-2www/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:30:50 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Netflix’s newest program certifies post-production tools for Netflix Originals</Title>
            <Description>Netflix on Thursday announced a new program aimed at helping Netflix Originals artists and producers select the right tools for delivering their content to its streaming service. With the launch of the Netflix Post Technology Alliance, as the program is called, Netflix will now identify products from vendors that meet technical and delivery specifications today, and [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/iKD-KlR3Y-E/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:26:04 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Crypto’s second bubble, Juul has 60 days and three Chinese IPOs</Title>
            <Description>Hello and welcome back to Equity, TechCrunch’s venture capital-focused podcast where we unpack the numbers behind the headlines. After a long run of having guests climb aboard each week, we took a pause on that front, bringing together three of our regular hosts instead: Connie Loizos, Danny Chrichton, and myself. Despite the fact that there were [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/BxTFb0H9YE8/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:10:14 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mobile bank Chime picks up credit score improvement service Pinch in all-stock deal</Title>
            <Description>Chime, the no-fees mobile bank valued at $500 million as of its last round, has put some of its funds to use with its first acquisition. The deal is for Pinch, a startup that was focused on helping millennials and other young adults build better credit. It was best known for a service called PinchRent, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/MqWql8uvO8g/</URL>
            <Date>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 17:03:05 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Ostrichpillow Hood, the latest product from Studio Banana, is no joke</Title>
            <Description>I&amp;#8217;m not going to lie, when Studio Banana released the original Ostrichpillow back in 2012, despite breaking all Kickstarter records at the time, I thought the whole thing might be an elaborate joke. Or, worse still, since the sleep-at-your-desk styled product had found popularity amongst people who worked at startups, Silicon Valley was now parodying [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/o2DpAAgW3eU/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:00:15 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>On-demand delivery and moving app Dolly hits $1 million in revenue and expands into SF and DC</Title>
            <Description>The Seattle-based on-demand delivery and moving service, Dolly, is rolling out its services in San Francisco and Washington, DC, as it eyes a broader national expansion in the coming months after hitting a milestone of $1 million in monthly revenue earlier this year. The company, which raised $8 million in a 2015 funding round, currently [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/6G2Bsh3cux0/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:30:49 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Review: iPhone XS, XS Max and the power of long-term thinking</Title>
            <Description>The iPhone XS proves one thing definitively: that the iPhone X was probably one of the most ambitious product bets of all time. When Apple told me in 2017 that they put aside plans for the iterative upgrade that they were going to ship and went all in on the iPhone X because they thought [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/z_n5t7WwHCc/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:55:52 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Ultimate.ai nabs $1.3M for a customer service AI focused on non-English markets</Title>
            <Description>For customer service, Ultimate.ai&amp;#8216;s thesis is it&amp;#8217;s not humans or AI but humans and AI. The Helsinki- and Berlin-based startup has built an AI-powered suggestion engine that, once trained on clients&amp;#8217; data-sets, is able to provide real-time help to (human) staff dealing with customer queries via chat, email and social channels. So the AI layer [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/WvrWOxSQKSo/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 09:54:09 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Instacart expands ALDI partnership</Title>
            <Description>After pilot programs in Atlanta, Dallas, Los Angeles and Chicago were &amp;#8220;overwhelmingly positive,&amp;#8221; per Instacart CEO Apoorva Mehta&amp;#8217;s statement, the grocery delivery service has decided to expand its partnership with U.S. grocer ALDI. As of Thanksgiving, Instacart users in 35 states and 5,000 ZIP codes will be able to fill their virtual carts with ALDI [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/nygdjrnSfPw/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 09:00:56 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Divido, the consumer finance platform, scores $15M Series A</Title>
            <Description>Divido, the consumer finance platform that lets you take out credit at the point of purchase to help spread the cost of buying new things, has raised $15 million in Series A funding. Leading the round is Dawn Capital, and DN Capital, with participation from Mastercard, American Express Ventures and a number of previous investors. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/vFuyNXZkv0s/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 08:52:10 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lower prices and more access at Disrupt Berlin 2018</Title>
            <Description>How much do we love Berlin, home of one of the best international tech communities going? So much that Disrupt Berlin 2018, which takes place on 29-30 November, is our third time hosting our world-class tech conference in this edgy and exciting European city. We don’t rest on our laurels here at TechCrunch, and we [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/FrAMy14vqps/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 08:00:06 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Withings returns from the dead with Steel HR Sport watch</Title>
            <Description>Any time a smaller company is gobbled up by a larger one, you assume the worse. In the case of Nokia buying Withings, that’s more or less what happened. First Nokia launched a handful of products under its own name and ultimately dropped the French health hardware company altogether. Four months ago, one of Withings&amp;#8217; [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/V9F_WIkfEgk/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 07:05:02 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Google partners with Renault-Nissan-Mitsubishi to put Android into millions of vehicles</Title>
            <Description>Google will partner with Renault -Nissan-Mitsubishi, the largest auto alliance in the world by vehicle sales, to put Android-based infotainment systems into millions of cars, the companies told Wall Street Journal. The alliance’s next-generation infotainment system and dashboard displays will use Android and launch in 2021. Drivers will be able to access Google’s maps, app [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/f5clbdzu9tM/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 06:59:46 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Ola raises $50M at a $4.3B valuation from two Chinese funds</Title>
            <Description>Ola, the arch-rival of Uber in India, has raised $50 million at a valuation of about $4.3 billion from Sailing Capital, a Hong Kong-based private equity firm, and the China-Eurasian Economic Cooperation Fund (CEECF), a state-backed Chinese fund. The funding was disclosed in regulatory documents sourced by Paper.vc and reviewed by Indian financial publication Mint. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/VsVyA4MjSg0/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 05:05:20 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Audi partners with Amazon and Electrify America to help kickstart its EV ecosystem</Title>
            <Description>Audi is partnering with e-commerce giant Amazon and VW Group unit Electrify America as the automaker prepares to deliver its first all-electric SUV to U.S. dealerships next year. The Audi e-tron, which was unveiled Monday night in San Francisco, kicks off the German automaker&amp;#8217;s electric vehicle ambitions. The e-tron is the first of three battery-electric [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/E8WrAOvP1XM/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 04:54:07 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>How the Audi e-tron compares to the Tesla Model X and Jaguar I-Pace</Title>
            <Description>Audi just announced its first production electric vehicle. Called the e-tron, the EV is a mid-size SUV loaded with technology with an unofficial range of over 300 miles. It&amp;#8217;s nicely equipped, and with a starting price of $74,800, it sits between the Jaguar I-Pace and the Tesla Model X. The e-tron is most similar to [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/kBgeg6kMjoM/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 04:06:27 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The Audi e-tron SUV is an electric shot at Tesla</Title>
            <Description>This is the Audi e-tron. The electric SUV seats five, starts at $74,800 and in official Audi testing, experienced a range of well over 300 miles on a charge. The e-tron will hit Audi dealerships in the middle of 2019, and prospective buyers can reserve one right now for $1,000. This is Audi’s first production [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/MoEiKuMayOI/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 04:03:59 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Amazon’s ‘Marvelous Mrs. Maisel’ wins big at the Emmys</Title>
            <Description>Amazon&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel&amp;#8221; dominated the comedy categories at tonight&amp;#8217;s Primetime Emmy Awards, winning for outstanding comedy series, supporting actress in a comedy series (Alex Borstein), lead actress in a comedy series (Rachel Brosnahan), writing in a drama series (Amy Sherman-Palladino) and directing in a comedy series (Amy Sherman-Palladino). It&amp;#8217;s an impressive showing for [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/wsKQWbGTtLU/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 02:58:24 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Meet Yusaku Maezawa, the first private passenger to take SpaceX’s BFR around the moon</Title>
            <Description>Japanese billionaire and entrepreneur Yusaku Maezawa will be the first private citizen to take a flight around the moon in SpaceX&amp;#8217;s Big Falcon Rocket, a 240,000-mile journey slated for as early as 2023. In an emotional and jubilant speech during a SpaceX event Monday at the company&amp;#8217;s headquarters in near Los Angeles, Maezawa exclaimed &amp;#8220;I [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/6xNck8YxomU/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 02:27:48 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Africa’s Jumo raises $52M led by Goldman to bring its fintech services to Asia</Title>
            <Description>Asia&amp;#8217;s fintech scene is poised to get a little larger after Jumo, a company that offers loans to the unbanked in Africa, revealed plans to expand into the continent. To get the ball rolling, Jumo has opened an office in Singapore to lead the way and landed a massive $52 million investment led by banking giant [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/NiGxT_xMP90/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 01:00:02 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Twitter is bringing back the chronological timeline</Title>
            <Description>Your Twitter prayers are answered! Well, maybe not the prayers about harassment or the ones about an edit tweet button, but your other prayers. Today in a series of tweets, the company announced that it had heard the cries of its various disgruntled users and will bring back a form of the pure chronological timeline [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/FlMr6T44ouo/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:55:53 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Trump expands tariffs on China by another $200 billion, threatens more</Title>
            <Description>By this point, you should all know the drill. Another day, another massive tariff from the Trump administration. After rumors the past few weeks that the president was considering expanding tariffs to another $267 billion worth of imported goods from China, the administration announced today that it would expand them merely to another $200 billion [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/r-YHpzNxGQg/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:34:49 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Elon Musk extends Tesla’s free supercharging for life offer</Title>
            <Description>Tesla has been phasing out free unlimited access to its network of fast-chargers for a couple of years now. The last vestige of that program was a referral system that was supposed to expire at midnight Sunday. But it&amp;#8217;s been given new life for at least one more day, and perhaps even longer to buyers [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/xt1g3TSTxSE/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:22:11 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Apple’s iBooks revamp, Apple Books, is here</Title>
            <Description>Apple&amp;#8217;s new and improved iBooks app, now called Apple Books, has popped up on iPhones across the world today with the release of iOS 12, the software update available to download as of this morning. The new app has five tabs: Reading Now, Library, Book Store, Search and, for the first time, a dedicated Audiobooks tab. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/hVFy0Ev2yiI/</URL>
            <Date>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 23:39:37 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Captain Marvel is here to save the 90s in first trailer</Title>
            <Description>Brie Larson’s cosmic superhero couldn’t have asked for a better setup than Avengers: Infinity War (Caution — minor spoilers ahead, naturally). Revealed via Nick Fury’s (Samuel L. Jackson) period-inappropriate pager in the end credits, the scene showed off very little in the way of detail, save for the fact that superhuman is apparently the last [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/H4vXYqQ4-Wo/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:34:49 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>UIpath lands $225M Series C on $3 billion valuation as robotics process automation soars</Title>
            <Description>UIPath is bringing automation to repetitive processes inside large organizations and it seems to have landed on a huge pain point. Today it announced a massive $225 million Series C on a $3 billion valuation. The round was led by CapitalG and Sequoia Capital. Accel, which invested in the companies A and B rounds also [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/q1jtNOJcSKA/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:23:24 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>WayRay raises $80M at a $500M valuation led by Porsche for its holographic AR display tech</Title>
            <Description>The large, legacy car industry has pinned a lot of hopes and dreams on innovative startups to build the next generation of automotive technology, and today the latest chapter in that story was revealed. WayRay, a Zurich-based developer of holographic augmented reality technology and hardware &amp;#8212; used in head-up displays that project images into a driver&amp;#8217;s [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/xizNFz2CUFU/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:01:27 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mozilla’s Firefox Reality web browser is now available</Title>
            <Description>Mozilla&amp;#8217;s vision of a VR-first web browser is ready for consumers to download and judge. Firefox Reality is a browser built entirely for virtual reality. While you may have read about desktop Firefox or Chrome adding WebVR support, Firefox Reality is a web browser that you actually use entirely inside a VR headset. You can [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/88LGtjD0cjA/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:56 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Symantec offers free anti-spoofing services to US political campaigns and election groups</Title>
            <Description>Symantec is the latest private security company to offer its expertise to vulnerable political targets on the house. Today the company announced that it would extend its &amp;#8220;Project Dolphin&amp;#8221; service (dolphins eat phish, get it) to political campaigns, candidates and election officials, all &amp;#8220;prime target[s] for malicious actors seeking to influence the outcome of the [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/9_E3mpB-fHk/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:47 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Cloudflare’s new ‘one-click’ DNSSEC setup will make it far more difficult to spoof websites</Title>
            <Description>Bad news first: the internet is broken for a while. The good news is that Cloudflare thinks it can make it slightly less broken. With &amp;#8220;the click of one button,&amp;#8221; the networking giant said Tuesday, its users can now switch on DNSSEC in their dashboard. In doing so, Cloudflare hopes it removes a major pain-point [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/05RZTP9o9uw/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:44 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>UBTECH launches a STEM robotics building kit</Title>
            <Description>Here in the States, UBTECH is probably best know for the crazy-walking Star Wars Stormtrooper it released late last year. But the company’s been producing robotics toys for long enough to get a vote of confidence in the form of a $820 million Series C late last year. The Chinese company’s latest project takes a [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/itC-SrzXHhs/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:27 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Indigo raises $250M, launches marketplace to help farmers get paid for quality grain</Title>
            <Description>Indigo, the startup bringing algorithms and machine learning to the agricultural industry, has raised a $250 million Series E, bringing its total raised to $650 million. The funding values the company at $3.5 billion, according to a source familiar with the deal. That&amp;#8217;s a steep increase from its previously reported value: $1.4 billion with a [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/JmL8-5UL6qs/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:15 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Mabl announces $20 million Series B to bring automated QA to enterprise customers</Title>
            <Description>Mabl, a Boston-based startup from the folks who brought you Stackdriver, wants to change software testing using machine learning, and today it announced a $20 million Series B investment led by GV (formerly Google Ventures). Existing investors CRV and Amplify Partners also participated. As part of the deal, Karim Faris, general partner at GV will [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/AkdGFy00cMk/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:06 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Erectile pharmacy app Roman raises $88M to launch ‘quit smoking’ kit</Title>
            <Description>Roman is a rocket ship, and I&amp;#8217;m not talking about how it sells Viagra and Cialis. Less than a year after launching its cloud pharmacy for erectile dysfunction with $3 million in funding and a five-person team, Roman has grown to seventy team members and a revenue run-rate in the 10s of millions &amp;#8212; up [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/cKeo_OIn1wU/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:59:50 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Marketing data startup Singular raises $30M</Title>
            <Description>Singular, a startup working to unify data for marketers, is announcing that it has raised $30 million in Series B funding. The company was founded by former Onavo executives, including Gadi Eliashiv, Eran Friedman and Susan Kuo — who now serve, respectively, as Singular&amp;#8217;s CEO, CTO and COO. Eliashiv explained that Singular was created in [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/UXiVFH2iYUc/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:44:26 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>UiPath lands $225M Series C on $3 billion valuation as robotic process automation soars</Title>
            <Description>UiPath is bringing automation to repetitive processes inside large organizations and it seems to have landed on a huge pain point. Today it announced a massive $225 million Series C on a $3 billion valuation. The round was led by CapitalG and Sequoia Capital. Accel, which invested in the companies A and B rounds also [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/q1jtNOJcSKA/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:23:24 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Zumper raises $46M more to take on Zillow and the rest with its apartment rental platform</Title>
            <Description>While the property market in the US appears headed for a slowdown, a startup that&amp;#8217;s honing in on rentals is doubling down on growth. Zumper, a San Francisco-based startup that has built an end-to-end platform to source, rent out and help service apartments across the US, has raised another $46 million in funding &amp;#8212; money [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/2VCFC-Ev76U/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:08:42 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Buy tickets for concerts on TV with the new Comcast and Ticketmaster feature</Title>
            <Description>Comcast and Ticketmaster are rolling out a feature to let Xfinity X1 customers search tour dates and begin the ticket buying process directly through their televisions &amp;#8212; using voice search on their remotes. The feature&amp;#8217;s launch coincides with the first tickets going on sale for Kelly Clarkson&amp;#8217;s new tour. If users speak &amp;#8220;Kelly Clarkson tour&amp;#8221; [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/p2ELi8Sqn9c/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:00:27 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>12 years in, TechStars doubles down on corporate relationships</Title>
            <Description>The goal of any accelerator is to back startups that are reaching exponential growth. Sometimes, though, the accelerator itself hits that inflection point. TechStars, which was founded in 2006, has expanded aggressively over the past twelve years. Once a single accelerator program for a handful of early-stage startups in Boulder, the program now encompasses 44 [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/YEdD3wPgGY4/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:00:44 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>iRobot i7+ initial impressions</Title>
            <Description>After its go around my apartment, the i7+ is “still learning.” It’s fitting sentiment for the new Roomba, which iRobot is positioning as much as a platform as a robotic vacuum. Like a smartphone, it’s designed to learn new tricks over the life of the product, through over the air updates. In this particular case, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/KgNgz-6e6JA/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:18:46 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Instagram will promote mid-term voting with stickers, registration info</Title>
            <Description>Facebook is getting ready to purposefully influence the U.S. mid-term elections after spending two years trying to safeguard against foreign interference. Instagram plans to run ads in Stories and feed powered by TurboVote that will target all US users over 18 and point them towards information on how to get properly registered and abide by [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/OJ7wfeAPyqE/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:17:28 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Rent the Runway opens physical store in San Francisco</Title>
            <Description>Rent the Runway, the fashion startup that began as a rental service for special occasions and has since evolved over the last couple of years into a service for people also looking to spice up their everyday wear, just opened up its fifth physical, standalone location. The new location, in downtown San Francisco, enables Rent the [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/uCqic_wNDHA/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:05:56 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Behold Ubisoft’s gloriously ridiculous Assassin’s Creed Amazon Echo</Title>
            <Description>The Assassin’s Creed Odyssey Echo Plus is a limited edition, which will no doubt make fans want the thing that much more. It’s a standard Amazon device that Ubisoft dressed up in a Spartan helmet, to be given away in small quantities through the company’s site. The ridiculous thing is the game maker’s way of [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/-3zNMJBr6Mg/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:00:49 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Spire Health Tags are now on Apple’s shelves</Title>
            <Description>Spire&amp;#8217;s Health Tags, the dark and tiny devices you stick on your clothes to gather all sorts of health data from your steps, heartbeat and stress levels is now available at your local Apple Store. The company started out with a breath tracking device to detect when you are feeling tense and help calm you down. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/GsKONiNPxXk/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:00:48 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Maison Me nabs $1M from Google’s Assistant fund and more for made-to-order clothes</Title>
            <Description>Amazon&amp;#8217;s focus on using its camera-enabled Echo devices to help you figure out what to wear everyday has highlighted how the tech world sees a big opportunity in building fashion-related tools and services beyond the now-ubiquitous but still quite basic business of e-commerce, where clothes are displayed on websites, and ordered for delivery to your home. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/L1G11muA-6k/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:24:30 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>State Department confirms data breach exposed employee data</Title>
            <Description>The State Department has confirmed a data breach affecting an unknown number of employees. A spokesperson told TechCrunch that the breach affected &amp;#8220;less than 1 percent&amp;#8221; of unclassified employee inboxes. &amp;#8220;We have not detected activity of concern in the Department’s classified email system.&amp;#8221; &amp;#8220;We determined that certain employee personally identifiable information may have been exposed [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/dmJGMxPRj5U/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:12:39 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Amazon’s new toolkit helps developers build Echo-connected accessories</Title>
            <Description>Amazon wants developers to build their own Alexa Gadgets. As you may recall, Amazon last year launched its own gadgets &amp;#8211; those weird, Bluetooth-connected Echo Buttons &amp;#8211; but told us this year at CES that it had plans to open up gadget-building to the wider developer community. Now, it has. The company today is launching [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/uF_NChr0Kvk/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:12:12 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>The Gap Table: Women own just 9% of startup equity</Title>
            <Description>Even bigger than the salary gap that sees women earn $.82 on the dollar is the equity gap. A new study from Carta and the ex-Twitter female investor group #Angels reveals that women make up 35 percent of startup equity-holding employees, yet own just 20 percent of the equity. That means they own just $0.47 [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/XaamaofnT5M/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:08:55 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Illumix raises $8.6M to build more dynamic phone-based AR games</Title>
            <Description>As iOS12 drops, we are again reminded that phone-based AR is on hundreds of millions of phones but we still haven&amp;#8217;t seen any big successes built on the new technologies. Illumix is hoping that its approach to building games that understand where the user is while serving up content that responds to that space can [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/xNdHVlCz4z0/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:00:54 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lyft hits 1 billion rides a couple of months after Uber hit 10 billion trips</Title>
            <Description>Today marks a big milestone for Lyft &amp;#8212; one billion rides. That&amp;#8217;s a milestone Uber hit in December 2015. Uber has since grown to 10 billion trips completed &amp;#8212; including Eats deliveries &amp;#8212; as of this past July. Uber, of course, had a bit of head start given it launched in 2009 while Lyft first [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/c_c46X9FZIo/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:00:19 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Framer X design tool steps in the ring with InVision, Adobe, and Sketch</Title>
            <Description>Design tools are becoming increasingly important to just about every brand out there. Today, a new entrant joins the race. Framer X, a revamped version of three-year-old Framer, was founded by Koen Bok and Jorn van Dijk after the duo sold design software Sofa to Facebook in 2011. Framer X is a rich, React-based design [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/jWbx_2LM4lA/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:00:07 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Lyft deploys electric scooters in Santa Monica</Title>
            <Description>Lyft has launched its electric scooters in Santa Monica, Calif. as part of the city&amp;#8217;s pilot program, joining both Bird and Lime, CNET first reported. As part of the pilot program, Lyft can have up to 250 scooters on the streets at any one time. Riders must also be sure to stay within the service [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/pZagiAH92sM/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:57:52 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Google’s parental control software Family Link expands to teens</Title>
            <Description>Google&amp;#8217;s parental control software for mobile devices, Family Link, will now help parents of teenagers, too. The company announced this morning the addition of new features aimed at parents of children over the age of 13. Perhaps the most controversial choice Google has made with this expansion is that teens can choose to turn off [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Tipg206c_yc/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:47:21 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Postmates raises another $300M, reportedly valued at $1.2B</Title>
            <Description>On-demand delivery service Postmates announced this morning that it has raised $300 million in additional funding led by Tiger Global Management. While the company&amp;#8217;s press release doesn&amp;#8217;t mention this, Fortune reports that the deal valued Postmates at $1.2 billion. Tiger&amp;#8217;s Scott Schleifer is joining the board of directors. Postmates does say that it&amp;#8217;s completing &amp;#8220;millions&amp;#8221; [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/sLCQWEOOlVc/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:46:50 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Facebook named in suit alleging job ads on its platform unlawfully discriminated against women</Title>
            <Description>Facebook&amp;#8217;s ad platform is facing charges that it has enabled gender-based discrimination against millions of women in a class action suit filed on behalf of three female workers and backed by the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU). The legal action also names ten employers who are alleged to have used the social media giant&amp;#8217;s platform [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/3ozjADsBlO8/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:43:41 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>12 years in, Techstars doubles down on corporate relationships</Title>
            <Description>The goal of any accelerator is to back startups that are reaching exponential growth. Sometimes, though, the accelerator itself hits that inflection point. Techstars, which was founded in 2006, has expanded aggressively over the past twelve years. Once a single accelerator program for a handful of early-stage startups in Boulder, the program now encompasses 44 [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/YEdD3wPgGY4/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:00:44 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Nintendo is offering an exclusive Fortnite bundle with the Switch</Title>
            <Description>Fortnite has taken the world by storm. In fact, the game is so popular that Epic has released versions for PC, Xbox, PS4, iOS, Android and the Nintendo Switch, making the game about as accessible as possible. The popularity of the game stems from the general popularity of the Battle Royale genre and popular streamers [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/1MEeoeLhWog/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 18:33:12 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Old media giants turn to VC for their next act</Title>
            <Description>The Web 1.0 and Web 2.0 eras weren’t kind to the world’s largest media conglomerates, throwing their business models into question, creating whole new categories of content consumption, and bringing online competition to subscription and ad pricing. Many of the media giants from the 1990s and early 2000s remain market leaders with multi-billion dollar valuations, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/6nflUg8VrRg/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 18:28:46 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Coinbase poaches LinkedIn’s head of data Michael Li</Title>
            <Description>Coinbase continues to beef up its management team with another new hire in Michael Li, who&amp;#8217;s joining the cryptocurrency trading platform as its VP of data. Li spent the last seven years at LinkedIn, most recently as its head of analytics and data science. &amp;#8220;Data will be essential to empowering Coinbase’s mission, and core to company’s [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/58Kuscq-SWE/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:57:20 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Hulu with Live TV tops a million subscribers</Title>
            <Description>Hulu&amp;#8217;s live TV streaming service has hit a milestone number of more than 1 million subscribers. That&amp;#8217;s up from the estimated 450,000 CNBC reported at the beginning of the year, and the 800,000 official number Hulu announced in May. But although the live TV audience may be growing, it&amp;#8217;s still a small fraction of Hulu&amp;#8217;s [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/vW1xcwRcQzM/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:32:44 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Answering its critics, Google loosens reins on AMP project</Title>
            <Description>Accelerated Mobile Pages, or AMP, has been a controversial project since its debut. The need for the framework has been clear: the payloads of mobile pages can be just insane, what with layers and layers of images, Javascript, ad networks, and more slowing down page rendering time and costing users serious bandwidth on metered plans. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Xq4qo8cmPSk/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:13:45 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Apple has finished paying $15 billion European fine</Title>
            <Description>Apple has finished wiring billions of euros to pay back illegal tax benefits to the Irish government according to Reuters. Overall, Apple has paid $15.3 billion (€13.1 billion) for the original fine as well as $1.4 billion (€1.2 billion) in interests. In August 2016 the European Commission ruled that Apple benefited from illegal tax benefits [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/5VQ72nXeX78/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:07:24 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>HQ Trivia teases upcoming Wheel of Fortune-style mobile game</Title>
            <Description>HQ Trivia is gearing up to debut a follow-up to its wildly popular live mobile game show. Called HQ Words, the company announced this morning they&amp;#8217;ll release the Wheel of Fortune-style game in October. HQ Words. Coming this October. pic.twitter.com/e1TbDSHvV5 &amp;#8212; HQ Trivia (@hqtrivia) September 18, 2018 HQ Trivia, which airs twice per day and awards [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/7dvvYyTNAA4/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:03:08 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Peter Thiel’s argument that Silicon Valley has been ‘brainwashed’ by higher education is tired</Title>
            <Description>Billionaire VC Peter Thiel has largely flown under the radar since raising his hand to support Donald Trump&amp;#8217;s presidential bid, then working with Trump&amp;#8217;s administration to fill some of its many vacant positions. The association made him deeply unpopular in Silicon Valley, though he says people have not shown a &amp;#8220;great deal of hostility to [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/3n8muNng1Do/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:46:54 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Early-bird sale ends this Friday for TC Sessions: AR/VR in Los Angeles</Title>
            <Description>After Friday, September 21, ticket prices for TC Sessions: AR/VR will jump $100 for the October 18 event hosted at UCLA. Buy your early-bird $99 tickets today before these savings fly the coop!</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/7a8x7cdNT9Y/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:30:42 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>DOJ launches investigation into Tesla, Elon Musk’s tweets</Title>
            <Description>Tesla&amp;#8217;s stock is down 5 percent this morning after news emerged the U.S. Department of Justice had launched a criminal investigation into CEO Elon Musk&amp;#8217;s Aug. 7 tweets about taking the company private. The criminal probe is in addition to the previously reported Securities and Exchange Commission investigation into the electric car company. “Last month, following [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/fQ_c1s-ZO7o/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:30:34 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>YouTube to shut down standalone Gaming app, as gaming gets a new home on YouTube</Title>
            <Description>YouTube will no longer maintain a separate app targeting gaming and live game streaming, the company announced today. The YouTube Gaming app, which first arrived in 2015, will be sunset sometime next spring as its host of features make their way over to YouTube&amp;#8217;s main site. Over the years, the YouTube Gaming app has been [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/66GLl4uEwUk/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:30:27 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Inside the pay-for-post ICO industry</Title>
            <Description>In a world where nothing can be trusted and fake news abounds, ICO and crypto teams are further muddying the waters by trying &amp;#8211; and often failing &amp;#8211; to pay for posts. While bribes for blogs is nothing new, sadly the current crop of ICO creators and crypto projects are particularly interested in scaling fast [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/e-6dsOsLI4U/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:26:27 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Microsoft launches new AI applications for customer service and sales</Title>
            <Description>Like virtually every other major tech company, Microsoft is currently on a mission to bring machine learning to all of its applications. It&amp;#8217;s no surprise then that it&amp;#8217;s also bringing &amp;#8216;AI&amp;#8217; to its highly profitable Dynamics 365 CRM products. A year ago, the company introduced its first Dynamics 365 AI solutions and today it&amp;#8217;s expanding [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/BGyqoKeyeGQ/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 19:00:09 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Title>Microsoft is putting HoloLens to work with new Dynamics 365 applications</Title>
            <Description>Microsoft HoloLens mixed reality glasses have always been interesting technology, but it&amp;#8217;s never been clear how the company would move from novelty device to actual viable business use cases. Today, it made a move toward the latter, announcing a couple of applications designed to put the HoloLens to work in Dynamics 365, giving it a [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/bswD4Hf8xd0/</URL>
            <Date>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 19:00:09 +0000</Date>
        </Entry>
    </Entrys>
</root>
