<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
    <Entrys>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Chat fiction startup Hooked unveils ‘Dark Matter,’ its first feature-length thriller</Title>
            <Description>Chat fiction startups have been exploring the types of stories that you can tell in the form text message conversations, and now Hooked is taking that exploration one step further with the launch of &amp;#8220;Dark Matter.&amp;#8221; The company describes this as its first feature-length story. &amp;#8220;Dark Matter&amp;#8221; tells the story of Tasneem (Taz) Singh, a [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/BRZAMdEj0LM/</URL>
            <Date>16:32 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Tap, a new startup from Sam Rosen, wants to be the Google of drinking water</Title>
            <Description>MakeSpace founder and former CEO Samuel Rosen is ready to launch his next venture, and it has little or nothing to do with the on-demand economy. This time, Rosen is setting his sights on the world of water. Tap aims to be the world&amp;#8217;s first public index and global search engine for drinking water. Plastic [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/xhebRnJyY2Q/</URL>
            <Date>16:19 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Epic Games, the creator of Fortnite, raises $1.25 billion</Title>
            <Description>It pays to have the most popular game in the world. Epic Games, the creators of the runaway gaming smash hit Fortnite, have raised $1.25 billion in a new round of financing. via GIPHY It&amp;#8217;s been 20 years since Epic Games first released its Unreal game development engine in concert with its first person shooter, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/I7ejeE08Kx8/</URL>
            <Date>16:16 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Blockchain partners with Ledger for its hardware wallet</Title>
            <Description>Blockchain startup Blockchain shared its roadmap for the coming months. The company is launching a hardware wallet in partnership with Ledger. Blockchain is also launching a new trading platform called Swap — this platform will find the best trading prices across a variety of exchanges and liquidity pools so that you can exchange tokens at [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/YcoC2mlnxyE/</URL>
            <Date>16:12 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>What to expect from Apple’s iPad event</Title>
            <Description>Thrills? Chills? iPads? Definitely yes on that last one, at least. The invites are out and the rumors have been pouring in, fast and furious. On Tuesday October 30, the company will be wrapping up hardware season with one final event, hitting all of the points that didn’t quite make it into September’s big iPhone [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/z54T-UaMVz0/</URL>
            <Date>16:00 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>More than half of crypto news sites are pay-for-play</Title>
            <Description>In a clever bit of sleuthing by Corin Faife at Breaker, we find that over half of the most popular crypto blogs offer pay-for-play posts including &amp;#8220;CEO interviews&amp;#8221; that are not labelled as sponsored. Further, many sites offer premium services in which blog writers will repost PR content without a sponsored tag. As I noted [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/ilpGBjNrm1o/</URL>
            <Date>15:34 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Samsung reportedly debating foldable phone form factor and the S10’s headphone jack</Title>
            <Description>Samsung’s foldable phone has been floating around the company under the codename “Winner” for some time now. That bit of info isn’t new. It’s understandably taken the company a while to get the thing just right. After all, we’re talking a new paradigm here in terms of form factor. It’s an exciting process, indeed — [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/7wW1iWbVcgU/</URL>
            <Date>15:24 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>You can now use Alexa to move around inside apps like Netflix and Hulu on Fire TV Cube</Title>
            <Description>Amazon is making it easier to use Alexa to do more than launch apps and streaming services on Fire TV devices, but to also navigate once inside them. The company confirmed it quietly launched an update specifically for Fire TV Cube devices that allows device owners to use Alexa instead of a remote control for [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/k20SidYzS3s/</URL>
            <Date>14:56 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Microsoft closes its $7.5B purchase of code-sharing platform GitHub</Title>
            <Description>After getting EU approval a week ago, today Microsoft&amp;#8217;s acquisition of GitHub, the Git-based code sharing and collaboration service with 31 million developers, has officially closed. The Redmond, WA-based software behemoth first said it would acquire GitHub for $7.5 billion in stock in June of this year, and after the acquisition closed it would continue to [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/N4vZ0XTcWOE/</URL>
            <Date>14:41 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Market turmoil, billion dollar funds, and the Qualtrics IPO</Title>
            <Description>Hello and welcome back to Equity, TechCrunch’s venture capital-focused podcast, where we unpack the numbers behind the headlines. This week the normal band was together, with Connie Loizos, Danny Crichton, and myself on hand along with IVP investor Jules Maltz. We had yet another episode of market turmoil, that was again reversed to some extent before [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/3EmMwzmex-g/</URL>
            <Date>14:10 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>WhatsApp is finally adding stickers</Title>
            <Description>WhatsApp is finally adding stickers to its hugely popular messaging app. The company said today that support for stickers will roll out to Android and iOS users over &amp;#8220;the coming weeks.&amp;#8221; Initially, the app&amp;#8217;s 1.5 billion users will have a seemingly limited selection with the first packs provided by WhatsApp&amp;#8217;s own design team and some &amp;#8220;other [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Q_eT1PIp-7g/</URL>
            <Date>11:03 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Valentin Stalf to talk about scaling N26 at Disrupt Berlin</Title>
            <Description>We couldn’t put together a conference in Berlin without inviting Valentin Stalf from N26, the co-founder and CEO of one of Europe&amp;#39;s most promising startups. A few years ago, few people would have bet on a startup creating a bank from scratch. N26 now has over 1.5 million clients and a ton of funding. N26 [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Hps-u3NT-Tg/</URL>
            <Date>08:17 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>China’s NIO invests in LiDAR startup Innovusion</Title>
            <Description>Innovusion, a two-year-old startup developing LiDAR sensor technology for autonomous vehicles, has raised $30 million in a Series A funding round co-led by Chinese firms Nio Capital and Eight Roads Ventures along with U.S.-based F-Prime Capital. Other seed round and strategic investors joined the round, the startup said. Nio Capital is the venture arm of [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/dwrtdHazIAA/</URL>
            <Date>04:35 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>As Tether flails, cryptocurrency exchanges launch rival stablecoins</Title>
            <Description>The promise of Tether, the digital currency pegged 1:1 to the US dollar, was that it could provide the benefits of a cryptocurrency while providing a fiat -backed peg against price fluctuations. But the currency has fallen below the $1 in recent weeks, right as a range of competing currencies are becoming available to meet [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/wpyBt-UCf58/</URL>
            <Date>04:04 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Quizlet hits 50M monthly users</Title>
            <Description>Following a $20 million round earlier this year, Quizlet is seeing solid growth in revenue and MAUs.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/fnXqZOV7HXA/</URL>
            <Date>24:20 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Two hackers behind 2016 Uber data breach have been indicted for another hack</Title>
            <Description>Two hackers who stole millions of users&amp;#8217; data from ride-hailing firm Uber have been indicted on separate hacking charges related to a data breach at online learning portal Lynda, two people familiar with the case have told TechCrunch. Vasile Mereacre, a Canadian citizen living in Toronto, and Brandon Glover, a Florida resident, were indicted earlier [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/2-JMCd1y8Xg/</URL>
            <Date>24:17 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Inspired by spiders and wasps, these tiny drones pull 40x their own weight</Title>
            <Description>If we want drones to do our dirty work for us, they&apos;re going to need to get pretty good at hauling stuff around. But due to the pesky yet unavoidable restraints of physics, it&apos;s hard for them to muster the forces necessary to do so while airborne — so these drones brace themselves against the ground to get the requisite torque.</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/CeREsqkSZQ0/</URL>
            <Date>23:54 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Vishal Makhijani steps down as chief executive of Udacity</Title>
            <Description>Vishal Makhijani, the longtime chief executive of online education company Udacity, is stepping down as its chief executive officer, TechCrunch has learned. Makhijani first joined the company in 2013 as chief operating officer under Sebastian Thrun, the company&amp;#8217;s founder and chief executive at the time. In 2016, Thrun, the original architect of Alphabet&amp;#8217;s self-driving car [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/PrS3blyH54E/</URL>
            <Date>23:29 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Amazon shares fall as record profits are offset by conservative holiday forecasts</Title>
            <Description>Amazon is still raking in the cash, but its slower than expected customer growth in its web services offerings and a weaker than expected sales outlook for the holiday season shook investor confidence and caused the stock to slide around 5 percent in after-hours trading. Profits for the company continued to soar, reaching $2.9 billion, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/Zhj_YGVYll8/</URL>
            <Date>23:03 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Anker announces a new speaker, projector and tiny wall charger</Title>
            <Description>Master of all things gadget accessory, Anker announced a handful of new products at an event tonight in Manhattan. The biggest/smallest of the bunch is the PowerPort Atom, a compact wall charger designed to free up spaces around an outlet. The $30 device sports a USB-C port and is smaller than most standard smartphone chargers. [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/qrUZUTLm8Tk/</URL>
            <Date>23:00 25/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>Reelgood acquires Guidebox to bring streaming TV data to more places</Title>
            <Description>Reelgood, a startup aimed at helping cord cutters find shows and movies to watch on the services they subscribe to, has made an acquisition in the hopes of bringing Reelgood&amp;#8217;s data to more places. The company has bought Guidebox, a streaming availability data provider which powers Roku, TVGuide, Metacritic and others. Deal terms weren&amp;#8217;t disclosed, [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/KOVmCeOhJ8M/</URL>
            <Date>16:52 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <FeedTitle>TechCrunch</FeedTitle>
            <Title>China’s ByteDance leapfrogs Uber to becomes world’s most valuable startup</Title>
            <Description>Move aside Uber, China&amp;#8217;s ByteDance is now the world&amp;#8217;s highest-valued tech startup. That&amp;#8217;s according to reports from Forbes and Bloomberg both of which claim that the company has completed a $3 billion investment that values the company at $75 billion. A source with knowledge of the deal confirmed the round to TechCrunch and suggested that [&amp;#8230;]</Description>
            <URL>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Techcrunch/~3/jwJ9uopfAfE/</URL>
            <Date>16:51 26/10/2018</Date>
        </Entry>
    </Entrys>
</root>
